<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 15:49:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Coconut oil (remix)</title>
		<link>/coconut-oil-remix/</link>
					<comments>/coconut-oil-remix/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 04:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bargain Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hair]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kitchen Sink Beauty]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>So, I&#8217;m sitting here watching &#8220;Daredevil,&#8221; and, it occurs to me that I am the true daredevil because I am currently giving coconut oil as a hair treatment a second chance. I haven&#8217;t washed it out yet, so, to put it in daredevil terms, I&#8217;m still waiting to see if my suicycle make it over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/coconut-oil-remix/">Coconut oil (remix)</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[</p>
<p>So, I&#8217;m sitting here watching &#8220;Daredevil,&#8221; and, it occurs to me that I am the true daredevil because I am currently giving coconut oil as a hair treatment a second chance. I haven&#8217;t washed it out yet, so, to put it in daredevil terms, I&#8217;m still waiting to see if my suicycle make it over the metaphorical dog doo stick. &nbsp;</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/IMG_3884.gif" alt="">&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="/coconut-oil-hair-mask-results-show/">Last time I used coconut oil in my hair</a>, it was a reeeeeal shitshow. I used way too much oil, and I doused every strand from scalp to end. I mean I went TO TOWN with the coconut oil. My head was greasy for days. This time, I used just a few tablespoons of the coconut oil mixed with a couple drops of Rosemary oil, and I only applied it to my scalp. This coconut oil experiment also has a different hypothesis; &nbsp;I&#8217;ve been reading about scalp massage to stimulate hair growth, and, hey, sounds good to me. I&#8217;m into oils and massages and sensual things like that. It&#8217;s also well documented that I&#8217;m very into growing locks so long and luscious that I no longer require tops. I massaged my scalp really well, ran the excess oil on my hands through the length of my hair, twirled it all up in my trusty claw clip, and now, I&#8217;m just letting the oil do what it do. Whatever that is.&nbsp;</p>
</p>
<p>We&#8217;ll see how things work out when I take a shower. Fool me once, coconut oil! Fool me once.&nbsp;</p>
<p><b>UPDATE:</b>&nbsp;I was really scared I was going to end up using dish soap to wash my hair like I had to after the time I used too much oil to remove an ill conceived glue-in quick weave, and no amount of traditional shampoo would degrease me. But, I pulled out the big guns AKA my Pureology clarifying shampoo, and there weren&#8217;t any problems washing out the coconut oil. Obviously, I can&#8217;t tell yet if this really helps with hair growth, but, at least my scalp doesn&#8217;t feel all toight and flaky like it often does after I wash and dry my hair. I&#8217;m thinking this Sunday night scalp massage might become part of my weekly beautifying treatment regimen. It felt divine, it smelled good, my hair is soft, my roots aren&#8217;t greasy, and my scalp isn&#8217;t dry. I made it over the dog doo stick!&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/coconut-oil-remix/">Coconut oil (remix)</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/coconut-oil-remix/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Melt&#8217;s Dark Room Returns!</title>
		<link>/melts-dark-room-returns/</link>
					<comments>/melts-dark-room-returns/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 18:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lipstick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Melt Cosmetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Upcoming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back in November, Melt Cosmetics released their newest shade, a juicy, plummy color named Dark Room. When the site went live with the product drop, it was a madhouse. Luckily, having survived the great Missoni for Target Frenzy of 2011, I was prepared. When the dust settled and the lipsticks were sold out, I had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/melts-dark-room-returns/">Melt&#8217;s Dark Room Returns!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1122 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/melt-dark-room-873x1024.png" alt="melt dark room" width="696" height="816" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/melt-dark-room-873x1024.png 873w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/melt-dark-room-256x300.png 256w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/melt-dark-room.png 888w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px" /></p>
<p>Back in November, Melt Cosmetics released their newest shade, a juicy, plummy color named Dark Room. When the site went live with the product drop, it was a madhouse. Luckily, having survived the great Missoni for Target Frenzy of 2011, I was prepared. When the dust settled and the lipsticks were sold out, I had my tube, and all was right in my world. Kind of dumb to not buy two, but, I was really in the zone and I had my eyes on the prize.</p>
<p>If you missed the chance to jump on this color in November, it&#8217;s coming back in stock, and it&#8217;s going to be permanent.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1123 size-large" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-collage-1024x1024.jpg" alt="Melt Dark Room collage" width="696" height="696" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-collage-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-collage-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-collage-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-collage-1272x1272.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-collage.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Miss you, nails.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Melt described this lipstick color as the inside of a beet, and that&#8217;s pretty accurate. It&#8217;s a really rich, sumptuous shade. I liked it best with multiple layers blotted down. It&#8217;s matte, and it wears really well. I did a friend&#8217;s makeup for her wedding, and we used it to give her a dramatic lip for the reception.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1124 " src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-pics-1024x1024.jpg" alt="Melt Dark Room pics" width="647" height="647" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-pics-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-pics-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-pics-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-pics-1272x1272.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Melt-Dark-Room-pics.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 647px) 100vw, 647px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>The babely bride and yours truly, wearing Dark Room. </em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Dark Room will be back in stock on February 4th, so if you want it, get your credit card all cleaned, sharpened, and ready to go. From what I can tell, when Melt restocks, the supply doesn&#8217;t last long. Get out there and chase that lipstick! Have you ever experienced the rush of successfully snagging your coveted product during one of these madhouse cosmetics releases? It&#8217;s a very triumphant feeling. AND, 7-10 days later, there&#8217;s lipstick at your door! BONUS.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.meltcosmetics.com/products/dark-room">Buy Dark Room by Melt Cosmetics <strong>HERE</strong>!</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/melts-dark-room-returns/">Melt&#8217;s Dark Room Returns!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/melts-dark-room-returns/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DIY Try: Watercolor Mug</title>
		<link>/diy-try-watercolor-mug/</link>
					<comments>/diy-try-watercolor-mug/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DIY]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Links]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nails]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1118</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m always on the lookout for new projects to start and abandon. I can&#8217;t help it, I&#8217;m just really passionate about half knitted scarves! Unfinished crafts are my life&#8217;s work. Every once in a while, I screw up, and one gets done. Like these DIY watercolor mugs I found from Poppytalk. photo via Poppytalk Gorgeous, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/diy-try-watercolor-mug/">DIY Try: Watercolor Mug</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m always on the lookout for new projects to start and abandon. I can&#8217;t help it, I&#8217;m just really passionate about half knitted scarves! Unfinished crafts are my life&#8217;s work.</p>
<p>Every once in a while, I screw up, and one gets done. Like these DIY watercolor mugs I found from <a href="http://www.poppytalk.com/2014/07/diy-watercolor-mug.html">Poppytalk</a>.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class=" aligncenter" src="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-EYB0c4IUXB4/U9XppeMC00I/AAAAAAABN_U/HE-jW40bx7Y/s1600/Final2.jpg" alt="" width="700" height="464" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>photo via Poppytalk</em></p>
<p>Gorgeous, right? I had the idea to put that lovely splash of color on a white ceramic pot as a birthday gift for a green thumbed friend! In my mind, she opens the box, pulls out the pot, and gets a tear in her eye from my beautiful, and very expensive looking, gift that was made all the more special by the fact that I did it with my own little hands. It was a very, very good plan.</p>
<p>Would the owner of this one of a kind piece of functional artwork please raise her hand?</p>
<p>&#8230;</p>
<p>&#8230;</p>
<p>Ok. I never sent it.</p>
<p>I have a good reason though! It came out, umm, not so good. She would have cried a little tear, but not from being overwhelmed by beauty and friendship.</p>
<p>Sorry, Missy.</p>
<p>Happy birthday?</p>
<p>This was extremely perplexing because my trial run came out pretty nice!</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1119" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/watercolor-mug.jpg" alt="watercolor mug" width="640" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/watercolor-mug.jpg 640w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/watercolor-mug-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/watercolor-mug-300x300.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></p>
<p>Before I did the pot, I tried the process on a mug. It&#8217;s cool! I would have been happy if the pot had come out like this! I&#8217;m really sad it didn&#8217;t. I kind of feel like I know what I did wrong though, and I want to try it again. I&#8217;ve got nail polish <a title="Pretty Ladies All In a Row" href="/pretty-ladies-row/">out the yang</a>, and a lot of free time. Missy&#8217;s birthday might not be licked yet!</p>
<p>I bet you&#8217;re waiting to see the fucked up pot. Well, too bad. It&#8217;s too crusty looking, and it would bring great shame to our household. I&#8217;ll show it off when I get it right! Fingers crossed!</p>
<p><a href="http://www.poppytalk.com/2014/07/diy-watercolor-mug.html">See Poppytalk&#8217;s Watercolor Mug tutorial HERE.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/diy-try-watercolor-mug/">DIY Try: Watercolor Mug</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/diy-try-watercolor-mug/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dog stuff and blog stuff</title>
		<link>/dog-stuff-blog-stuff/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 19:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I greatly prefer winter weather to summer weather. Like, maybe I have reverse SAD. Days upon days of cloudy weather doesn&#8217;t bother me, but, day after day of blistering sun makes me feel crazy and desolate. Stepping outside first thing in the morning to a full blast sun puts me in a cranky mood. Some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/dog-stuff-blog-stuff/">Dog stuff and blog stuff</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I greatly prefer winter weather to summer weather. Like, maybe I have reverse SAD. Days upon days of cloudy weather doesn&#8217;t bother me, but, day after day of blistering sun makes me feel crazy and desolate. Stepping outside first thing in the morning to a full blast sun puts me in a cranky mood. Some summer stuff, like spending a day with a friend alternating between dozing on floating rafts and working out a synchronized swimming routine to &#8220;Man, I Feel Like a Woman,&#8221; is quite divine. Other stuff, like, oh, everything else, is awful. What&#8217;s good? Kids are out of school, it&#8217;s a thousand degrees, people keep trying to stuff me full of BBQ and then put me in a bathing suit &#8211; it&#8217;s a nightmare. Winter isn&#8217;t totally awesome, I&#8217;m not going to pretend I&#8217;m not freezing my balls off. I get cold all the way to the bone, I just don&#8217;t care because that&#8217;s why I have chi dogs and big blankets.</p>
<p>Speaking of chi dogs, someone would like to make his big blog debut today.</p>
<p>Weighing in at 2.3 pounds!</p>
<p>One half of the Tiny Twin Titans of Terror!</p>
<p>I may or may not have been in the grips of a fever delirium when I bought him from a couple standing outside Target with puppies in a laundry basket!</p>
<p>Ladies and gentlemen, allow me to introduce the hardest playing boy in chi business, Mr. Please, Please Don&#8217;t Pee There&#8230;</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Gomez &#8220;Dr. Teeth&#8221; Cosper!</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1112" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Gomez-e1421862041964.jpg" alt="Gomez" width="640" height="640" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>&#8220;Dr. Teeth&#8221; isn&#8217;t his middle name, it&#8217;s just his most apropos nickname. </em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Isn&#8217;t he a ladykiller?!</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1114" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/acquitted-gif.gif" alt="acquitted gif" width="480" height="360" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">He&#8217;s a teeny baby, barely three months old, and he&#8217;s just disgustingly cute. Wrinkly neck, ears too big to hold up, curly whiskers! He&#8217;s the total package! Even Rowdy came around and now she&#8217;s a big sister.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1113" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Rowdy-and-Gomez-e1421863356325.jpg" alt="Rowdy and Gomez" width="640" height="640" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>just big sister things</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">He&#8217;s a baby genius, he&#8217;s a big chicken, and we love the crap out of him. He&#8217;s kind of a willful prick sometimes, and not a day goes by where he doesn&#8217;t try to eat my hair, but, nobody&#8217;s perfect!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">¯\_(ツ)_/¯</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">In other news, when was the last time you watched this?</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="David Lee Roth - Just A Gigolo / I Ain&#039;t Got Nobody (1985) (Music Video - Dave TV Version)" width="696" height="392" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ui-zBq-f5XA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>This song and its video are one of my go-to cures for the blahs. I was feeling kind of blah this morning because of my cold toes and my poor, poor frozen succulents (RIP), but Diamond Dave turned it all around. It&#8217;s impossible not to laugh, and dance, and sing along! I mean, I fucking dare you to not AT LEAST do some jazz hands. You can&#8217;t do it. This is why we were only meant to have him for so long; if he had stayed on top forever we&#8217;d all be dead from high kicks.</p>
<p>What song always cheers you up? Do you agree with Jason that we missed an opportunity to name Gomez &#8220;David Chi Roth?&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/dog-stuff-blog-stuff/">Dog stuff and blog stuff</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Easy Peasy Manikreezy</title>
		<link>/easy-peasy-manikreezy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Floss Gloss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nail Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nails]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicole by OPI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I was, like, not made to live without a beauty team. I guess I can do my own nails, but it&#8217;s really better if someone else does them. I&#8217;m a Real Housewife, not a real housewife. Know what I mean? It&#8217;s not like I&#8217;m particularly bad at doing my nails. I used to be pretty [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/easy-peasy-manikreezy/">Easy Peasy Manikreezy</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I was, like, not made to live without a beauty team. I guess I can do my own nails, but it&#8217;s really better if someone else does them. I&#8217;m a Real Housewife, not a real housewife. Know what I mean?</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not like I&#8217;m particularly bad at doing my nails. I used to be pretty good at it until several months of fills and fresh sets ruined me. I don&#8217;t know! I&#8217;m so bad at the edges now! This entire mani was invented around avoiding my GD cuticle edges.</p>
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/xiWzLDLEk-/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="13" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);">
<div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/xiWzLDLEk-/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> </p>
<div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;">
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div>
<div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div>
<div style="padding-top: 8px;">
<div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div>
</div>
<div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div>
<div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;">
<div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div>
<div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div>
</div>
<div style="margin-left: 8px;">
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div>
<div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div>
</div>
<div style="margin-left: auto;">
<div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div>
<div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div>
<div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div>
</div>
</div>
<p></a> </p>
<p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/xiWzLDLEk-/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank">I like to think up manicures that don&#39;t require precision. At first I wasn&#39;t sure about this one, but now I REALLY like it. Once I cleaned up the splash zone, it looks pretty good! Details!!! ????Bottom layer &#8211; DONATELLA and MOON BABY by @flossgloss ???? top color &#8211; GIVE ME THE 1ST DANCE by @nicolebyopi ???? #beauty #nails #flossgloss #moonbaby #donatella #nicolebyopi #liveinthecolor #nailswag #nailsofinstagram</a></p>
<p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;">A post shared by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/thelabbunny/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"> Sarah Cosper</a> (@thelabbunny) on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2015-01-07T02:58:44+00:00">Jan 6, 2015 at 6:58pm PST</time></p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<p><script async src="//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"></script></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Allll the areas around my actual nails are the splash zone. Mani specifically designed around avoiding this situation, and I&#8217;m still &#8220;cleaning up&#8221; my nails in the shower. ACK!</p>
<p>OH WELL. This nail art(?) is great because it doesn&#8217;t need tape, a steady hand, or, extra brushes. I didn&#8217;t even need to sit at the kitchen table to get a level work surface. I did the whole thing kicked all the way back on the couch. I&#8217;ll tell you how!</p>
<p>You&#8217;re going to need three colors; two for the base, and one for on top. I used two Floss Gloss colors, DONATELLA and MOON BABY, for the base, and GIVE ME THE 1ST DANCE by Nicole by OPI for the top.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/IMG_2710.jpg"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="  aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/IMG_2698.jpg" alt="IMG_2698.JPG" width="600" height="600" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><i>L &#8211; R: <a href="http://flossgloss.com/collections/lacquers/products/moon-baby">MOON BABY</a>, <a href="http://flossgloss.com/collections/lacquers/products/donatella">DONATELLA</a>, GIVE ME THE 1ST DANCE</i></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">First, make haphazard swipes of your base colors on the bottom 3/4 of your nails. Do all ten fingers.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Then, working one nail at a time, dab some of your top color on the tip, sort of lightly pulling the color upwards.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Wipe all the polish off the brush, onto the lip of the bottle.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Drag the brush from the tip to the top of your nail. I liked the silver color for this because it gave everything an antique looking finish. You might need to dab more polish here and there, depending on where you want the coverage. Just make sure you wipe all the excess off the brush for the thinly layered areas. If at any point, your coverage with this color gets too solid, take a q-tip soaked in polish remover, and gently roll it over the areas you want to thin out.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Cover it all with a top coat, and you&#8217;re done!</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/IMG_2710.jpg"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="  aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/IMG_2710.jpg" alt="IMG_2710.JPG" width="673" height="673" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>OF COURSE I got polish on my finger here.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">You sort of can&#8217;t fuck this up. I mean, you can, but, it&#8217;s hard. My first finger looked like garbage compared to the rest of them. But, by the time I got to the end, they were looking exactly how I&#8217;d hoped. I was even able to go back and fix the ugly one with my q-tip trick! Just be patient with yourself, work with the dabbing and brushing, and you&#8217;ll get the hang of it!<span style="line-height: 1.5;"> </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="/easy-peasy-manikreezy/">Easy Peasy Manikreezy</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peep this! DUPE THAT</title>
		<link>/peep-dupe/</link>
					<comments>/peep-dupe/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 17:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bargain Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dupes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Instagram]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Links]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I love makeup and spending money (and chihuahuas, and pizza, and Jane the Virgin, and big d). I really hate being broke (and bell peppers, and Monty Python, and mansplainers). Thankfully, the diligent swatchers over at one of my favorite Instagram accounts, DUPE THAT, are all over the buying lots of makeup/still having money dichotomy. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/peep-dupe/">Peep this! DUPE THAT</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I love makeup and spending money (and chihuahuas, and pizza, and Jane the Virgin, and big d). I really hate being broke (and bell peppers, and Monty Python, and mansplainers).</p>
<p>Thankfully, the diligent swatchers over at one of my favorite Instagram accounts, DUPE THAT, are all over the buying lots of makeup/still having money dichotomy. They&#8217;re in there every day, showing us how often we&#8217;re paying extra for luxury brand names. When you collect lipsticks like I do, this is some valuable information.</p>
<blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-version="4" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);">
<div style="padding:8px;">
<div style=" background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;">
<div style=" background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAAGFBMVEUiIiI9PT0eHh4gIB4hIBkcHBwcHBwcHBydr+JQAAAACHRSTlMABA4YHyQsM5jtaMwAAADfSURBVDjL7ZVBEgMhCAQBAf//42xcNbpAqakcM0ftUmFAAIBE81IqBJdS3lS6zs3bIpB9WED3YYXFPmHRfT8sgyrCP1x8uEUxLMzNWElFOYCV6mHWWwMzdPEKHlhLw7NWJqkHc4uIZphavDzA2JPzUDsBZziNae2S6owH8xPmX8G7zzgKEOPUoYHvGz1TBCxMkd3kwNVbU0gKHkx+iZILf77IofhrY1nYFnB/lQPb79drWOyJVa/DAvg9B/rLB4cC+Nqgdz/TvBbBnr6GBReqn/nRmDgaQEej7WhonozjF+Y2I/fZou/qAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;"></div>
</div>
<p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://instagram.com/p/x2G_ESieCu/" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_top">It only took some playing in our collection to realize that we had a dupe for Lime Crime&#39;s Airborne Unicorn! @nyxcosmetics macaron lippie in Violet looks just like Airborne Unicorn, and even more vivid if possible! We love this bright lip color! </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Look at that! Every post is this good. They&#8217;re doing the Lord&#8217;s work over there.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.dupethat.com/">DUPE THAT recently launched a full site.</a> The site is searchable for brands and color names, thereby fixing the one issue I had with their IG only operation. It&#8217;s very exciting!!</p>
<p>Are you off today? Maybe spend some time browsing their site and making lists. Are you working today? My suggestion still stands. Your boss says it&#8217;s cool!</p>
<p><a href="http://www.dupethat.com/">Check out DUPE THAT&#8217;s full site, HERE!</a></p>
<p><a href="http://instagram.com/dupethat">See their Instagram page, HERE!</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/peep-dupe/">Peep this! DUPE THAT</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/peep-dupe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World&#8217;s Easiest Resolution</title>
		<link>/worlds-easiest-resolution/</link>
					<comments>/worlds-easiest-resolution/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bargain Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blemish Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cetaphil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cleansers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maintenance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skincare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1099</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m not a resolutions person. Obviously. I mean, here I am, knocking the dust off this blog well into the second (technically third) week of January. A resolutions person would have been here that first Monday. To me, New Year&#8217;s resolutions are amateur hour. I&#8217;m making and breaking promises to myself 365, BAYBAY!! My problem [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/worlds-easiest-resolution/">The World&#8217;s Easiest Resolution</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m not a resolutions person. Obviously. I mean, here I am, knocking the dust off this blog well into the second (technically third) week of January. A resolutions person would have been here that first Monday. To me, New Year&#8217;s resolutions are amateur hour. I&#8217;m making and breaking promises to myself 365, BAYBAY!!</p>
<p>My problem is, I always go too big. Lose weight, save money, find my life&#8217;s purpose, blah blah. That stuff is a lot of work! You know what&#8217;s probably way better for our mental well-being? Starting small. Make your bed every day! Kick your panties into the hamper instead of leaving them sunny-side up in the bathroom! Mop!<br />
No. Don&#8217;t mop. I&#8217;m sorry I said that. FUCK mopping.</p>
<p>How about, instead, you could resolve to have cleaner skin? You don&#8217;t even have to buy a new face wash, or an expensive cleansing brush. Are you all ready for my ONE WEIRD TRICK?</p>
<p>Here it is:</p>
<p>Wash your face longer. For 60 whole seconds. That&#8217;s it.</p>
<p>Real talk, you guys; I know what you&#8217;re doing. I see how quickly you wash your face. I SEE YOU. But, it&#8217;s ok! I used to do the same thing! In fact, I considered myself a pretty accomplished face washer. I washed my face every night and most mornings, I used my Clarisonic. I would even wash my face when I was three sheets to an ill wind! Some of the mascara might be left behind, but, I&#8217;d AT LEAST use a cleansing wipe. So, pretty good, right? Pretty good, but could be better. Like, maybe better if I didn&#8217;t rush through it in just a few seconds. You know, like how washing a fork with soap real fast is good, but making sure you get all the crud off is preferable?</p>
<p>Still not convinced? (Pretend you&#8217;re not convinced.) Will a little bit of Beauty School Confidential help? Consider this; a big reason for the effectiveness of a spa facial is the extensive time spent on cleansing. Most estheticians will cleanse your skin twice during a facial. When all is said and done, you&#8217;re going to get, probably, a combined five minutes of solid cleanser on skin action. It&#8217;s not an accident that your skin is so bright after that! I mean, the <em>default</em> time on my Clarisonic is 60 seconds, and that thing is using sonic vibrations, or whatever, AND bristles. If the Clarisonic needs 60 seconds to get your face clean with all that technology behind it, your sweet lil fingers need at least that long. It&#8217;s so easy though! A big part of this cleaner face resolution is the simplicity, because hopefully, you&#8217;re already washing your face. So, you don&#8217;t have to do a whole new thing, you just have to a regular thing differently.</p>
<p>&#8220;But, Sarah,&#8221; you might be thinking, &#8220;60 seconds is a long time to count! What if I get bored or lose my place? What if I count too fast or too slow? How am I supposed to keep track of the time when I&#8217;m in the shower in all my nudely glory?!&#8221; It&#8217;s easy! Zones, guys. It&#8217;s all about zones. Your forehead? ZONE. Nose down to your chin? ZONE. Those precious cheeks? ZONE(S). Three zones, 20 seconds each. That&#8217;s all you need to do to get cleaner skin. It&#8217;s free, it&#8217;s easy, it works!</p>
<p>Since I&#8217;ve been making an effort to wash my face more thoroughly, I&#8217;ve seen a visible improvement in my skin. I have a lot less tiny white heads around my eye/cheek area, and, I haven&#8217;t been getting random, underground, throbbing, volcanic breakouts on my jaw and chin. I even managed to avoid the inevitable eruptions I deal with whenever I get sick, and those are usually really gross, and really hard to kill.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1101 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/clean-skin-e1421386030944.jpg" alt="clean skin" width="540" height="540" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">HASHTAG NO FILTER</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">HASHTAG NO FOUNDATION, too. That&#8217;s right. No foundation. I have on a little concealer around my nose to cover some tissue related redness, and, I have on a little under eye brightener. But, that&#8217;s it. No foundation, no powder. No filter! Just my clean, moisturized skin. For comparison, here&#8217;s an unedited photo from the end of last summer.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1102 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/clean-face-comparison-e1421387573768.jpg" alt="clean face comparison" width="540" height="540" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I think you can tell a difference. In the first picture my skin looks brighter, clearer, and smoother. I&#8217;m wearing a full face in this photo, and my skin still doesn&#8217;t look as good. See what I&#8217;m saying? I&#8217;m not making it up!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I don&#8217;t even use an expensive cleanser.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1104" src="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/cetaphil-cleanser.jpg" alt="cetaphil cleanser" width="300" height="400" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/cetaphil-cleanser.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2015/01/cetaphil-cleanser-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em><a href="http://www.walgreens.com/store/c/cetaphil-daily-facial-cleanser-lotion/ID=prod351435-product">Cetaphil Daily Facial Cleanser, $7.49, Walgreens</a></em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Bet you didn&#8217;t think it was going to be THAT cheap. A cheap cleanser and your free fingers. That&#8217;s all you need. It&#8217;s really so easy! Easier than losing weight, easier than kicking your underwear into the hamper, easier than pretty much most things, and you get nicer skin. Happy freaking New Year! So fresh and so clean in 2015!</p>
<p>The post <a href="/worlds-easiest-resolution/">The World&#8217;s Easiest Resolution</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/worlds-easiest-resolution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask</title>
		<link>/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/</link>
					<comments>/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 18:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blemish Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dr. Jart+]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sephora, $7.50 for one sheet or $35 for a box of five A couple weeks ago, I hit the Sephora with a fellow childless enabler, and we had a lot of fun! Fun is a nice way of putting it. Rampage is a more accurate way of putting it. Like, did you know they have a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/">Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1091" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask.png" alt="dr jart mask" width="456" height="557" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask.png 456w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask-245x300.png 245w" sizes="(max-width: 456px) 100vw, 456px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/pore-minimalist-mask-P386840?skuId=1622380"><em>Sephora, $7.50 for one sheet or $35 for a box of five</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">A couple weeks ago, I hit the Sephora with a fellow childless enabler, and we had a lot of fun! Fun is a nice way of putting it. Rampage is a more accurate way of putting it. Like, did you know they have a sample limit at Sephora? Me neither! They way they told us, it seemed more like a suggestion, so we just kept hammering the samples anyways. I feel like my mid-level Sephora card entitles me to whatever I want in there. My VIB card, and my remaining bitterness over them making it seem like I had a job, and then not hiring me eight years ago. Last year, I made it a goal to let go of old grudges and annoyances, but that Sephora snub still stings. Especially when I saw homeboy that looks like Bobby fucking Hill working in there.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I like to just stay mad about not getting the job that one time so I don&#8217;t have to go back and try again. STAY MAD. That&#8217;s what I always say. That job is probably so hard; you have to deal with petty assholes like me all day. BUT, there is lipstick&#8230;.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">In my defense, it&#8217;s not like I just go in and demand all the samples and don&#8217;t buy anything. That&#8217;s not a rampage. A rampage involves damage inflicted on a personal level, too. If you&#8217;re not swiping your debit card in a near blackout state, sister, you ain&#8217;t rampaging.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Amidst the frenzy, in a fog of Tom Ford fragrances, I grabbed one of these single sheet Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Masks. Having never used a sheet mask before, I wasn&#8217;t sure what to expect. Since it was a sebum sucking and pore cleansing mask, I thought I&#8217;d get something sticky, or clay like. Instead, I got a fairly heavy mask that was absolutely drenched in a thin serum. Really, at that point, I was kind of confused, but, hey, I&#8217;m not a doctor! Dr. Jart is the doctor.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-1092" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask-photo-768x1024.jpg" alt="dr jart mask photo" width="546" height="728" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>-1 point for not having a mouth zipper.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After smoothing the mask onto my face, I realized, unless I kicked back, I was going to have a drippy mess to clean. I did not want that, and I didn&#8217;t want to waste any of that precious serum, so I put my head on my little pillow, and just <em>CHILLED.</em> The serum was really cool and relaxing, without any of the burning you can get from mint extracts.<i> </i>When the time was up, I peeled off the mask, and I was really surprised by how much serum my skin had absorbed. The mask wasn&#8217;t wet and heavy anymore, it was damp and papery. The directions said not to rinse, to just massage the remaining serum into the skin, and I am so about that. I hate washing off masks! I get so much water everywhere, it really might make more sense for me to just get in the shower. Same amount of toweling off, less water on the floor.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I wasn&#8217;t ready for how effective this mask was! My skin was smooth and clear, my underground sebum deposits were smaller, and my nose pores looked so clean. The work on the hard little sebum bumps was especially impressive; I&#8217;ve never seen a mask make  a noticeable difference on those before! Those disgusting little beads of oil are my #1 annoyance right now, so this turned me into repeat customer. Next time, I&#8217;m buying the whole box!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/pore-minimalist-mask-P386840?skuId=1622380">Buy Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p>The post <a href="/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/">Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On the Thumb</title>
		<link>/thumb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 23:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DIY]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floss Gloss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nail Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nails]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1087</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>That title is more like, On the Dumb. But, ACTUALLY, like On the Run. On the Run? They should have called that show, &#8220;Get Your Fucking Life for Three Hours.&#8221; I&#8217;ve watched that HBO special two and a half times, and I haven&#8217;t stopped yelling at Bey to kill &#8217;em all dead. She&#8217;s doing it, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/thumb/">On the Thumb</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>That title is more like, On the Dumb. But, ACTUALLY, like On the Run.</p>
<p>On the Run? They should have called that show, &#8220;Get Your Fucking Life for Three Hours.&#8221; I&#8217;ve watched that HBO special two and a half times, and I haven&#8217;t stopped yelling at Bey to kill &#8217;em all dead. She&#8217;s doing it, too!! I mean, I have this need for a beanie with one of those Roman soldier brush thingies on top, now!</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1326.jpg"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1326.jpg" alt="IMG_1326.JPG" width="498" height="744" /></a><br />
I&#8217;d stitch one up myself, but I&#8217;m a hundred percent sure the brush would just flop over like a melancholy rooster. And, also, I have no idea where you get one of those brushes.</p>
<p>On Saturday night, I had the champagne flowing, and the cheese plates stacked high. I don&#8217;t want to brag, but there were upwards of FIVE different kinds of cheeses. So, yeah. It was pretty fucking gross. I definitely got a stomach ache from all dat cheese. Worth it though!</p>
<p>In honor of the show, I broke out my <a href="http://emergingthoughts.com/Accessories/queen-beyonce-nail-decals.html">Sara M. Lyons &#8220;Queen Beyonce&#8221; nail decals</a>! I love these hilarious lil designs! They&#8217;re so perfect and cheeky! They&#8217;re also REALLY easy to apply; all you need are some small, sharp scissors, and a bowl of water. They&#8217;re basically temporary tattoos for your nails, they have the same application concept as that bitchin&#8217; ying-yang sign you bought out of the machine at the pizza parlor that one time.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1320.jpg" alt="IMG_1320.JPG" width="598" height="897" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Nails are one of my all time faves, Con Limon by Floss Gloss</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I fucked mine up by not using a lighter polish underneath them. As a result, Bey looks a little jaundiced. Jayndiced? Haha. Get it?<br />
Bey-Z looks better here:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1314.jpg" alt="IMG_1314.JPG" width="616" height="616" /><br />
<em>See? On the Thumb. Whomp, whomp.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Sara (probs too familiar) makes dope shit that really speaks to me. Like, her <a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/121781082/babewolf-sticker?">Babewolf</a>, or, her <a href="http://saramlyons.tumblr.com/post/29136201971/in-lux-we-trust-an-oldie-but-goodie">&#8220;In Lux We Trust&#8221; piece</a>, which is so awesome, it kind of makes me want to cry. I just realized I&#8217;m gushing, and I was gonna be all, &#8220;I&#8217;m a gusher,&#8221; but that&#8217;s not right. Let&#8217;s say, &#8220;I&#8217;m a fan.&#8221; That doesn&#8217;t sound as damp.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://emergingthoughts.com/queen-beyonce-nail-decals.html">These Bey decals are available only from Emerging Thought. Buy them HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="https://www.etsy.com/shop/saramlyons">Check out other sweet Sara M. Lyons stuff, HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p>The post <a href="/thumb/">On the Thumb</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MAC Heroine Lipstick</title>
		<link>/mac-heroine-lipstick/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Fave Looks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glasses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lipstick]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1079</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dat liner doe. I&#8217;m a sucker for a purple lip. Purple eyeshadow, too. I&#8217;m a sucker for purple eyeshadow. PURPLE NAILS! Don&#8217;t even get me started!! Long story short; I guess purple is my favorite color. Well&#8230;and black. Is leopard a color? No, that&#8217;s silly! Leopard is a neutral! &#8220;Leopard is a neutral,&#8221; has been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/mac-heroine-lipstick/">MAC Heroine Lipstick</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-1080" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-768x1024.jpg" alt="MAC Heroine" width="486" height="648" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-768x1024.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 486px) 100vw, 486px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Dat liner doe.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I&#8217;m a sucker for a purple lip.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Purple eyeshadow, too. I&#8217;m a sucker for purple eyeshadow.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">PURPLE NAILS! Don&#8217;t even get me started!!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Long story short; I guess purple is my favorite color.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Well&#8230;and black. Is leopard a color? No, that&#8217;s silly! Leopard is a neutral!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">&#8220;Leopard is a neutral,&#8221; has been my life motto since I was 16. I figured it out, and never looked back.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">WE&#8217;RE NOT PREACHING THE JOYS OF LEOPARD, SARAH. REMEMBER YOUR FIVE Gs.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1082" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/latrice-gif.gif" alt="latrice gif" width="500" height="280" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong><span style="text-align: left;">GOOD GOD, GET A GRIP, GIRL. </span></strong></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">The look above mixes up a purple lip with a leopard top, so I was pretty into it.  The lip is MAC&#8217;s Heroine, a vibrant, red-based purple. This color was a cult hit that MAC brought back, and made a part of their permanent collection. That&#8217;s good news because I could really see myself finishing this tube of lipstick. I mean, as soon as it came home, I made it a part of MY permanent collection (the zipper pouch inside my purse).</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Heroine has a satin finish, and it wears down to a bright matte that has a lot of staying power. I really appreciate that in a lip color. I love to do my makeup, but, I really hate having to constantly reapply my lip. I&#8217;m a modern woman! I don&#8217;t have time for that kind of nonsense. I don&#8217;t have time, and, also, I forget. And, also, pizza.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Oh, man. Pizza sounds so good right now. What time is it? 9:15?!?! Pizza isn&#8217;t even open yet. That&#8217;s ok. Everyone knows the sweetest pizza is the one you have to wait for.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">This lip color goes with all my favorite faces; neutral eye/bold lip, bold eye/bold lip, glasses/bold lip.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-1081" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-x-glasses.jpg" alt="MAC Heroine x glasses" width="516" height="516" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-x-glasses.jpg 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-x-glasses-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/09/MAC-Heroine-x-glasses-300x300.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 516px) 100vw, 516px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Glasses/bold lip goes ANYWHERE, with EVERYTHING. I love it! If you wear glasses, and you want some compliments, do it. People fucking love it. If you don&#8217;t have glasses, I feel bad for you, you&#8217;re obviously a dum-dum. Everyone knows glasses make you super smart. Glasses are also the best way to hide your true beauty. When you take them off, everyone is super impressed by how good looking and popular you are! WOWZA.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">This post, you guys, it&#8217;s not so good. I&#8217;m sorry. I accidentally took a summer vacation, now I&#8217;m super rusty!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-1083" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Rusty.png" alt="Rusty" width="471" height="312" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Rusty.png 400w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/09/Rusty-300x198.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 471px) 100vw, 471px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>ACTUAL SUPER RUSTY</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">That Rusty might be my favorite. I love the Anthony Michael Hall Rusty, but, this Rusty is hysterical to me. Those Rustys are tied for first? Second place is Nick Papagiorgio Rusty. David from Roseanne Rusty is neither here nor there for me.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.maccosmetics.com/products/spp/shaded.tmpl?CATEGORY_ID=CAT168&amp;PRODUCT_ID=PROD310">Buy Heroine by MAC HERE or in stores.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/mac-heroine-lipstick/">MAC Heroine Lipstick</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
