<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Josie Maran Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/josie-maran/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/josie-maran/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 18:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Josie Maran 100 Percent Pure Argan oil</title>
		<link>/josie-maran-100-percent-pure-argan-oil/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 18:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blemish Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Josie Maran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moisturizer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skincare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=990</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sephora, 1.7 oz., $48 Do people still say other people are &#8220;sprung?&#8221; Do people still get sprung? Can you be sprung on things that aren&#8217;t other people or their crotches? I&#8217;m not sure about the answer to any of these questions, so I&#8217;m going to take a big risk here when I say I am [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/josie-maran-100-percent-pure-argan-oil/">Josie Maran 100 Percent Pure Argan oil</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/josie-maran.jpg" alt="josie maran" width="450" height="450" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/josie-maran.jpg 450w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/05/josie-maran-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/05/josie-maran-300x300.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em><a href="http://www.sephora.com/100-percent-pure-argan-oil-P218700?skuId=1121797">Sephora, 1.7 oz., $48</a></em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p style="text-align: left;">Do people still say other people are &#8220;sprung?&#8221; Do people still get sprung? Can you be sprung on things that aren&#8217;t other people or their crotches? I&#8217;m not sure about the answer to any of these questions, so I&#8217;m going to take a big risk here when I say I am sprung on this Josie Maran Argan Oil.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BOI-OI-OI-OING!!!!!</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">That was the sound of me being sprung!! This blog is so high tech and interactive! Now, imagine you can smell lavender Febreze and chihuahua kisses&#8230;that&#8217;s right&#8230;..immerse yourself in the sounds and smells of my world.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I got a deluxe sample bottle of this Argan oil at Sephora a little over a month ago, and I am straight up obsessed. Although the bottle was small, it provided enough oil to find out that I love this product. I&#8217;ve been using it about twice a day, morning and evening, since I got it, and it has made a huge improvement  in my skin. I actually started using it in the first place because I was desperate. For the last couple months, my skin has been really off; it&#8217;s been dry, patchy, really uneven and super dull. My skin even looked yucky under my makeup! Foundation would cake up, or settle into creases. I HAD CREASES. It was bad. On top of THAT, I grew this zit on my chin that was throbbing, underground, and about the size of a pencil eraser.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Wait. Everyone knows what a pencil is, right? How old is everyone? Are pencils obsolete? Probably. Pencils were pretty obsolete 20 years ago. PENS FOREVER!!!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Are pens obsolete? Don&#8217;t care! I&#8217;ll never stop admiring my own name when written with a fancy pen.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Back to the face oil!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Like I said, since I&#8217;ve been using this oil, my skin has made a huge turnaround. It&#8217;s soft, smooth, bright, clear, and definitely younger looking. I even went out to fancy dinner and a show last week without wearing any face makeup! I just put on my oil after my shower, threw on some bronzer, and that was it. I looked like a gotdanged natural angel. This oil makes my skin, like, luminous. It works SO WELL, that I keep expecting strangers to come up to me out in public and demand to know what makeup I have on. Then, I&#8217;d be all, &#8220;I&#8217;m not wearing any makeup!&#8221; And they&#8217;ll be all, &#8220;What!? You&#8217;re so inherently beautiful! Here. Have a town car, chauffeur, and a modeling contract!&#8221; It hasn&#8217;t happened yet, but, like I said, I&#8217;ve only been using this oil for a month.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/100-percent-pure-argan-oil-P218700?skuId=1121797">Buy Josie Maran 100 Percent Pure Argan Oil HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p>The post <a href="/josie-maran-100-percent-pure-argan-oil/">Josie Maran 100 Percent Pure Argan oil</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
