<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Urban Decay Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/urban-decay/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/urban-decay/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 21:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Mrs. Mia Wallace</title>
		<link>/mrs-mia-wallace/</link>
					<comments>/mrs-mia-wallace/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 21:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Beauty Idols]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fave Looks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Urban Decay dropped their super limited edition Pulp Fiction themed collection this morning, and although I was interested, I had some struggles. The collection is small, only five pieces; an eyeshadow palette, red lipstick, liner and nail polish, and a glitter liner. Everything looks great, wearable and coordinated, but, I just couldn&#8217;t pull the trigger [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/mrs-mia-wallace/">Mrs. Mia Wallace</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1052" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/pulp-fiction-palette.jpg" alt="pulp fiction palette" width="570" height="570" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/pulp-fiction-palette.jpg 570w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/07/pulp-fiction-palette-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/07/pulp-fiction-palette-300x300.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 570px) 100vw, 570px" />Urban Decay dropped their super limited edition Pulp Fiction themed collection this morning, and although I was interested, I had some struggles. The collection is small, only five pieces; an eyeshadow palette, red lipstick, liner and nail polish, and a glitter liner. Everything looks great, wearable and coordinated, but, I just couldn&#8217;t pull the trigger on the shadow palette. I think between all the Naked palettes, including the Basics palette, I&#8217;m pretty covered as far as neutral shadows are concerned. As much as I&#8217;d like to add this palette to my pile, I think I have to pass.</p>
<p>You have to understand how much this hurt me. Two of my favorites things, UD shadow palettes and Pulp Fiction, are colliding! In faaaaaact, I&#8217;d say both UD and Pulp Fiction came into my life around the same time, 20 years ago. I can remember both the first time I bought a UD product, and the first time I watched Pulp Fiction. Combine that with the fact that the whole collection is based on one of my all time BANGS ICONS, Mia Wallace, and you get me in that makeup frenzy where I can&#8217;t think straight.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1053" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/mia-dance-gif.gif" alt="mia dance gif" width="490" height="340" /></p>
<p>I wore those bangs for 15 years, and I&#8217;ve been post-OD Mia Wallace for Halloween no less than three times. It&#8217;s not a stretch to call me a fan.</p>
<p>(**BEAUTY TIP** If you wear that Mia Wallace costume, complete with bloody nose and chest syringe, to the grocery store, <i>people will let you go to the front of the line because you look disgusting. **</i>END BEAUTY TIP**)</p>
<p>Lucky for me(?), my own BAD MOTHERFUCKER was in bed with me while I was loading up my online cart, and he reminded me that I had already decided to skip the shadows. He was right. I did decide that. I&#8217;m glad he&#8217;s around to keep me from accidentally snorting from the wrong baggie, or, buying eyeshadows I don&#8217;t need.</p>
<p>Not that I skipped the whole collection. I didn&#8217;t. I have the blood red &#8220;Mia Wallace&#8221; lip liner and lipstick coming to me, and you guys will see it soon! I wish I could afford to buy everything, just because I want it, but there are no super valuable briefcases around here. I am, however, available to take any and all falls for the right price. The falls don&#8217;t even have to be in boxing!</p>
<p>I am not available for watch storage.</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/pulp-fiction-2">Buy Urban Decay&#8217;s Pulp Fiction collection HERE.</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="/mrs-mia-wallace/">Mrs. Mia Wallace</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/mrs-mia-wallace/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Face Breakdown: Saturday Night Beaver</title>
		<link>/face-breakdown-saturday-night-beaver/</link>
					<comments>/face-breakdown-saturday-night-beaver/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 18:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Fave Looks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NYX Cosmetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1038</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to the freak nasty dude I live with for coming up with, &#8220;Saturday Night Beaver.&#8221; I&#8217;m a little obsessed with the glam and disco era of the 70s. I like glitter and dancing! I like freewheeling lifestyles! I like John Travolta! I don&#8217;t know, guys, I think I would have been really popular at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/face-breakdown-saturday-night-beaver/">Face Breakdown: Saturday Night Beaver</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-1039 " src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/disco-braids-768x1024.jpg" alt="disco braids" width="626" height="834" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/disco-braids-768x1024.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/06/disco-braids-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/06/disco-braids.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Thanks to the freak nasty dude I live with for coming up with, &#8220;Saturday Night Beaver.&#8221;</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I&#8217;m a little obsessed with the glam and disco era of the 70s. I like glitter and dancing! I like freewheeling lifestyles! I like John Travolta! I don&#8217;t know, guys, I think I would have been really popular at Studio 54. I&#8217;m a good time!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I want to start doing photo steps of these look breakdowns, but this one is super easy, so I&#8217;m just going to run through it.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">The eyes are all Urban Decay. First, I used &#8220;Gonzo&#8221; from the Electric Palette around the eye, all over the lid, and dragged it out towards my hairline. Then, on the inner corners, I used UD&#8217;s Heavy Metal Glitter Eyeliner in &#8220;Midnight Cowboy.&#8221; I also lightly patted some of the glitter on my temples, over the smudged out teal shadow. A matte nude shadow on the brow bone, and some mascara finishes the eye.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Lips were a fun combination of orange and gold. I used &#8220;Indie Flick,&#8221; a matte orange, by NYX Cosmetics. After that, I pressed a little bit of gold shadow into the center of my lips. I used &#8220;Half Baked&#8221; by Urban Decay.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I had so much fun with this look! I didn&#8217;t use it for anything, but Jason and Rowdy were really impressed! I mean, really, this was the hair day of my life. I wish it could look like this every day! My braiding skills still suck though, so I&#8217;ll just have to wait until the next time I can convince a friend to get her hands all up in my scalp.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I sent pictures of this look to my mom for an accuracy check, and she gave it her seal of approval. Let me tell you, she knows what she&#8217;s talking about, I&#8217;ve seen her do The Hustle.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">What do you guys think? I love it! Any questions?</p>
<p>The post <a href="/face-breakdown-saturday-night-beaver/">Face Breakdown: Saturday Night Beaver</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/face-breakdown-saturday-night-beaver/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Urban Decay Electric Pressed Pigment Palette Review and Looks!</title>
		<link>/urban-decay-electric-pressed-pigment-palette-review-looks/</link>
					<comments>/urban-decay-electric-pressed-pigment-palette-review-looks/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Eyeshadow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fave Looks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Electric Pressed Pigment Palette, Urban Decay, $49 I ordered this bad mamajama last Monday morning, when Urban Decay released it. It was in my mailbox on Friday, and I have looked exquisite every day since then. I haven&#8217;t really had anywhere to go, BUT, I&#8217;ve been looking foine while I&#8217;m cleaning toilets and wrapping dog [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-electric-pressed-pigment-palette-review-looks/">Urban Decay Electric Pressed Pigment Palette Review and Looks!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-966" alt="electric palette outside" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-outside-1272x954.jpg" width="705" height="529" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-outside-1272x954.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-outside-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-outside-1024x768.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 705px) 100vw, 705px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em><a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/what%27s-new/electric-pressed-pigment-palette/421.html">Electric Pressed Pigment Palette, Urban Decay, $49</a></em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I ordered this bad mamajama last Monday morning, when Urban Decay released it. It was in my mailbox on Friday, and I have looked <em><strong>exquisite</strong></em> every day since then. I haven&#8217;t really had anywhere to go, BUT, I&#8217;ve been looking foine while I&#8217;m cleaning toilets and wrapping dog pills in American cheese. Today, I&#8217;m going to wear a full face while I clean our room. Is that a fitting activity for the way I look today? No, but it looks like a dirty panty bomb went off in there, and I can&#8217;t keep living this way. Maybe this is other people&#8217;s idea of good room decor *coughJasoncough* but it ain&#8217;t mine. Also, I&#8217;m out of underwear.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">MOVING ON.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Back in the early years, crazy colors were what first drew me to Urban Decay. I was snapping up nearly every palette they released! The first few little ones, all the Book of Shadows palettes, Alice in Wonderland, the Anniversary Palette, Vice, more little ones! And that&#8217;s not even counting the single shadows I picked up. Then, around the time I started to feel like I had to tone it down a little, so did UD. So, then I bought all four of the Naked palettes! The Smoked palette! The Black Palette! I don&#8217;t think I need to tell you I don&#8217;t really have a lot of counter or drawer space. There are so many palettes, they have a dedicated cubby. Once the Naked palettes came around, I started doing my makeup way more neutral, and I had found myself wondering if I was ever going to go back to wearing a bright colored shadow. Honestly, as much as I used to love it, I didn&#8217;t know if it was me anymore.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Cue Urban Decay reading my mind again!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-967" alt="electic palette inside" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electic-palette-inside-1272x954.jpg" width="564" height="423" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electic-palette-inside-1272x954.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electic-palette-inside-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electic-palette-inside-1024x768.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 564px) 100vw, 564px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Top Row, L-R: Revolt, Gonzo, Slowburn, Savage, Fringe</em><br />
<em>Bottom Row, L-R: Chaos, Jilted, Urban, Freak, Thrash</em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-973" alt="electric palette swatches" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-swatches-1272x1052.jpg" width="545" height="451" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-swatches-1272x1052.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-swatches-300x248.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-swatches-1024x847.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-swatches.jpg 1912w" sizes="(max-width: 545px) 100vw, 545px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">GAH. Those are bright! When I first saw them, I was like, &#8220;I don&#8217;t know&#8230;.&#8221; Then, I bought them, and I was like, &#8220;OH. WAIT. I DO KNOW. I LOVE THEM.&#8221; I haven&#8217;t been able to keep my hands out of it. I even set up my makeup station at the kitchen table, and I look at the palette while I eat my Eggos. Syrup is part of my creative process, ok?</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">The powders are so silky and rich, they&#8217;re really beautiful. I&#8217;m talking HUGE color payoff, plus, they blend like buttah. I never stood a chance. UD enticed me back to bold colors, and I am happy about it! I used my matte UD eye primer for all of these looks except the last one when it occurred to me to try my white eyeshadow base. Also, I did my eyes before I did my foundation or anything else on my face. I didn&#8217;t actually get a lot of fall out from these shadows, but what does fall is so intense, you&#8217;ll want to be able to just sweep it away with a brush. I haven&#8217;t yet had the chance to use every color in the palette, but I plan on continuing to play with it, and I&#8217;ll post any other looks I do. For now, I have three looks to show you!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-968" alt="electric palette look 1" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-1.jpg" width="587" height="587" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-1.jpg 1632w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-1-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-1-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-1-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-1-1272x1272.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 587px) 100vw, 587px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I&#8217;m a sucker for cobalt blue; it&#8217;s one of my all time favorite cosmetics or accent colors. I had to try it first! It was flirting with me! Like, practically waggling its tongue at me, and we all know how ladies can&#8217;t resist that! This look was done using just Chaos on the lid, Revolt in the inner corners, and a matte nude from the Naked Basics palette to clean above the crease and up to the brow bone. I used a liquid liner on my top lid, and one of my black UD pencil liners on the bottom, the blush is actually the hot pink color, Savage, from the same palette, and I finished it off with UD&#8217;s Revolution lipstick in Naked. I&#8217;m sorry, but I looked really beautiful that day.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-969" alt="electric palette look 2" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-2.jpg" width="587" height="587" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-2.jpg 1632w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-2-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-2-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-2-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-2-1272x1272.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 587px) 100vw, 587px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Look Two was the easiest one to work up. I wet my brush with saline solution, and used Fringe as a liner on my top lid, with Freak lining the bottom lash line. I also dabbed Revolt into the corners of my eyes, and used Savage as blush again. Lips are UD&#8217;s Super-Saturated High Gloss Lip Color pencil in Crush. For some dumb reason, I forgot to take a picture of this one with my eyes closed. It&#8217;s too late now! We&#8217;re all just going to have to get on with our lives. I&#8217;m not sure how I feel about my mismatched earrings, is it like Janet Jackson, or, is it like a pirate? Is it like pirate Janet Jackson? Is there still such a thing as &#8220;the gay ear&#8221;? Do I look crazy? I think I like it, but I&#8217;m halfway through a bottle of wine right now.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-970" alt="electric palette look 3" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-3.png" width="587" height="587" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-3.png 1632w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-3-150x150.png 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-3-300x300.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-3-1024x1024.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-3-1272x1272.png 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 587px) 100vw, 587px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>GAZE UPON ME, IT&#8217;S ALLOWED. NO EYE CONTACT PLEASE.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I thought that first look was my favorite, and then I did this one. Are you freaking kidding me with this? UD&#8217;s purples have always been my favorites. It&#8217;s their signature color, they do it right, and Urban is no exception. For this look, I used the dark pink color, Jilted, in the crease, blended that forever, then added Urban to the lid, and blended THAT forever, too. I lined my top water line and lower lash line with the same black UD pencil, then, I smudged Urban underneath that. Once again, I used Revolt in the corners, and Savage on the cheeks. The lip color is a drugstore nude.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Also&#8230;.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-971" alt="electric palette look 4" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-4.jpg" width="587" height="587" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-4.jpg 1632w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-4-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-4-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-4-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-look-4-1272x1272.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 587px) 100vw, 587px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I couldn&#8217;t resist trying it with my all time favorite UD lip color. Jilted!!!! The addition of this lip color changed the whole look into something way bolder. Which is, like, amazing for a look that already boasts bright purple and dark pink eye makeup.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-972" alt="electric palette love" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-love.jpg" width="576" height="768" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-love.jpg 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-love-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/electric-palette-love-768x1024.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 576px) 100vw, 576px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>4 EVA</em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Do you see how we&#8217;re totally falling in love?</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">It&#8217;s my responsibility to inform you that some of these colors aren&#8217;t &#8220;approved&#8221; for use around the immediate eye area in the USA. From what I understand, they&#8217;re cleared in Europe, and that&#8217;s good enough for me. Just be aware if you have extremely sensitive eyes, I guess.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">So far, I have zero complaints about this palette. I&#8217;m so happy I bought it! I am looking dope and feeling good. The potency of this palette is so great that I bet nobody even noticed I need to get my eyebrows done. In fact, I bet nobody even noticed I wasn&#8217;t wearing pants in almost every picture. I am a master of mind control, and this palette has made me more powerful than ever!!!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/what%27s-new/electric-pressed-pigment-palette/421.html">Buy Urban Decay&#8217;s Electric Pressed Pigment Palette from UD HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/electric-pressed-pigment-palette-P385671?icid2=Urban_Decay_EditorsPicks_Carousel_P385671_link">From Sephora HERE.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-electric-pressed-pigment-palette-review-looks/">Urban Decay Electric Pressed Pigment Palette Review and Looks!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/urban-decay-electric-pressed-pigment-palette-review-looks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy it now! Urban Decay Electric Palette!</title>
		<link>/buy-now-urban-decay-electric-palette/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Eyeshadow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Upcoming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=959</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Urban Decay, $49 Naked is good. But, Naked-like hues probably aren&#8217;t what drew most of us to makeup. What drew us to makeup was COLOR. Bright blues, jewel purples, peacock greens!! Wheeeeeeeeee!!!! Urban Decay&#8217;s new Electric Pressed Pigment Palette is online, and it&#8217;s got everything you&#8217;d need to put some bold color back in your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/buy-now-urban-decay-electric-palette/">Buy it now! Urban Decay Electric Palette!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960" alt="ud electric" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/ud-electric.jpg" width="610" height="367" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/03/ud-electric.jpg 610w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/03/ud-electric-300x180.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 610px) 100vw, 610px" /><a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/electric-pressed-pigment-palette/landingpage-electricpalette.html">Urban Decay, $49</a></p>
<p>Naked is good. But, Naked-like hues probably aren&#8217;t what drew most of us to makeup. What drew us to makeup was COLOR. Bright blues, jewel purples, peacock greens!! Wheeeeeeeeee!!!!</p>
<p>Urban Decay&#8217;s new Electric Pressed Pigment Palette is online, and it&#8217;s got everything you&#8217;d need to put some bold color back in your life for Spring. At first, I wasn&#8217;t sure if I was going to order one. It&#8217;s been a looooong time since I wore shadow colors like this. But, I decided to go for it! IMMA SHAKE IT UP. So, now, I&#8217;m fucking pumped to get my electric pigments on!</p>
<p>I promise pics as soon as it shows up!</p>
<p><a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/electric-pressed-pigment-palette/landingpage-electricpalette.html">Buy the Urban Decay Electric Pressed Pigment Palette HERE.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/buy-now-urban-decay-electric-palette/">Buy it now! Urban Decay Electric Palette!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Double Trouble &#8211; Maybelline Color Tattoo Shadows in Barely Branded and Tough as Taupe</title>
		<link>/double-trouble-maybelline-color-tattoo-shadows-barely-branded-tough-taupe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coastal Scents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyeshadow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fave Looks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maybelline]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=936</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>  I&#8217;ve been working on this post for days! I&#8217;ve just been really distracted with, like, the Olympics, and learning to play ping pong, and I&#8217;ve had on pants and a bra SO MUCH this week, which is really, very unusual. Being seen in public a lot = less time sitting in front of my [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/double-trouble-maybelline-color-tattoo-shadows-barely-branded-tough-taupe/">Double Trouble &#8211; Maybelline Color Tattoo Shadows in Barely Branded and Tough as Taupe</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"> <img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-938" alt="color tattoo looks diptic" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-diptic.jpg" width="704" height="704" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-diptic.jpg 1632w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-diptic-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-diptic-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-diptic-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-diptic-1272x1272.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 704px) 100vw, 704px" /></p>
<p>I&#8217;ve been working on this post for days! I&#8217;ve just been really distracted with, like, the Olympics, and learning to play ping pong, and I&#8217;ve had on pants and a bra SO MUCH this week, which is really, very unusual. Being seen in public a lot = less time sitting in front of my laptop. Also, I think I was telling myself this post might suck and second guessing myself tons, so I was making everything more difficult. That&#8217;s just maybe laziness disguised as self esteem problems, though. I don&#8217;t know! I guess you guys will be the judge. If it sucks, I was right, and if it doesn&#8217;t suck, I&#8217;m maybe lazy, or I maybe have self esteem problems, or, maybe both. Let&#8217;s find out!</p>
<p>Last week, I finally got around to grabbing a few of those Maybelline Color Tattoo cream shadows, and now I am OBSESSED. I hate that I&#8217;ve been not buying them all this time! They&#8217;re so easy to work with, and the color is long lasting. I&#8217;ve used them almost every day since I got them, and I have fully planned to buy several more.</p>
<p>Today, I want to show you two looks I&#8217;ve done, using the same colors. Since the colors and placement are the same, the looks are similar, but they&#8217;re both so pretty and wearable, I had to show you guys both.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-937" alt="Color Tattoo Looks products" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/Color-Tattoo-Looks-products-e1392915925502.jpg" width="783" height="587" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/Color-Tattoo-Looks-products-e1392915925502.jpg 1632w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/Color-Tattoo-Looks-products-e1392915925502-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/Color-Tattoo-Looks-products-e1392915925502-1024x768.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 783px) 100vw, 783px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">These are the colors I used for these looks. We&#8217;ve got <strong>W.O.S.</strong> from Urban Decay&#8217;s Naked Basics palette, Maybelline Color Tattoo cream shadows in <strong>Barely Branded</strong> and <strong>Tough as Taupe</strong>, and a Coastal Scents shadow in <strong>Wild Raisin</strong>.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-945" alt="color tattoo looks swatches" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-swatches.jpg" width="768" height="476" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-swatches.jpg 1280w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-swatches-300x186.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-swatches-1024x635.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-looks-swatches-1272x789.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>L-R: Costa Riche liner, W.O.S, Tough as Taupe, Barely Branded, Wild Raisin</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Before I begin, I always use my Urban Decay Primer Potion. Then, on the first look only, I used W.O.S. on the entire lid; just to even out the skin, and to give the cream shadow something else behind it. Now for the fun part!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-939" alt="color tattoo look steps" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-steps.jpg" width="538" height="538" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-steps.jpg 1280w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-steps-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-steps-300x300.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-steps-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-steps-1272x1272.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 538px) 100vw, 538px" /></p>
<ol>
<li>Using a flatter brush, I applied Tough as Taupe over the lid, just to the crease.</li>
<li>Line the upper lash line and water line with a dark brown or grey liner; I used MAC&#8217;s Costa Riche. Smudge the line.</li>
<li>Using the pads of your fingers, gently pat Barely Branded around the edges of Tough as Taupe, blending upwards and onto the brow bone.</li>
<li>Apply Wild Raisin to the crease and the outer corner of the eye, then BLEND THE HELL OUT OF IT.</li>
</ol>
<p>And that&#8217;s it! If you want, you can lightly line your bottom lash line with the liner or the remaining product on the flat brush from the first step. Add some mascara, and you&#8217;re done!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-940" alt="color tattoo look 1" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-1.jpg" width="518" height="691" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-1.jpg 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-1-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-1-768x1024.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 518px) 100vw, 518px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Lips: UD&#8217;s Naked</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Look Two is exactly the same as Look One, except you switch Wild Raisin and Tough as Taupe. So, Wild Raisin will cover your lid, and Tough as Taupe will get blended into the crease. It looks like this:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-941" alt="color tattoo look 2 detail" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-2-detail.jpg" width="518" height="691" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-2-detail.jpg 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-2-detail-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-2-detail-768x1024.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 518px) 100vw, 518px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Lips: UD&#8217;s Protest</em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-943" alt="color tattoo look 2 close" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/color-tattoo-look-2-close1.jpg" width="518" height="691" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I&#8217;ve worn my makeup one of these two ways almost every day since last Friday. I just love how easy and flattering it is! And how awesome is it that these shadows are super cheap? I guess the Naked palette isn&#8217;t super cheap, but that color is also sort of unnecessary to the look, so who cares?! I&#8217;ve been doing this blog for almost a year, and the one thing I&#8217;ve learned is that my makeup snobbery has been keeping me from a lot of good makeup. Maybelline, in particular, has become a new favorite of mine. I never ever thought I&#8217;d be searching everywhere for a particular drugstore product like I do with high end brands, but here I am. It&#8217;s cool though, you know. Cheap products means more products, and Maybelline is always on sale, AND you can use your Ulta coupons on their stuff. I&#8217;m rolling in affordable cream shadows over here!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">What do you guys think? Do you have any questions?</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Buy Maybelline Color Tattoo shadows basically everywhere.<br />
<a href="http://www.coastalscents.com/wildraisin.html">Buy Wild Raisin from Coastal Scents <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/double-trouble-maybelline-color-tattoo-shadows-barely-branded-tough-taupe/">Double Trouble &#8211; Maybelline Color Tattoo Shadows in Barely Branded and Tough as Taupe</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Urban Decay Revolution Lipstick Spectacular</title>
		<link>/urban-decay-revolution-lipstick-spectacular/</link>
					<comments>/urban-decay-revolution-lipstick-spectacular/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 19:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=909</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s an extravaganza!!!!! Urban Decay Revolution Lipsticks, $22 each You guys remember back on Black Friday when Urban Decay had that amazing lipstick bundle? Six of their fabulous new Revolution Lipsticks for $50? Remember that? Remember how there was a very limited supply, but due to my vast internet shopping experience, fast fingers, and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-revolution-lipstick-spectacular/">Urban Decay Revolution Lipstick Spectacular</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s an extravaganza!!!!!</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910" alt="UD black friday boxes" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-black-friday-boxes.jpg" width="640" height="276" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-black-friday-boxes.jpg 640w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-black-friday-boxes-300x129.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/urban-decay/lipstick%2C-lip-stain-%26-gloss/revolution-lipstick/378.html">Urban Decay Revolution Lipsticks, $22 each</a></p>
<p><a title="Black Friday Spoils!" href="/black-friday-spoils/">You guys remember back on Black Friday when Urban Decay had that amazing lipstick bundle? Six of their fabulous new Revolution Lipsticks for $50? Remember that? Remember how there was a very limited supply, but due to my vast internet shopping experience, fast fingers, and the blinding power of my exposed nipples, I was able to grab one? </a></p>
<p>Remember?</p>
<p>Well, my lipsticks came in and I just hoarded them. They&#8217;ve been sitting on my desk all this time, waiting to be photographed and swatched. Getting more and more irrelevant by the second. While some people were yelling at Urban Decay on Facebook about there not being enough lipstick bundles for everyone, mine were unopened. It&#8217;s almost enough to make me feel like an asshole. ALMOST. But, I don&#8217;t! Those are MY lipsticks, MINE! I&#8217;ll preserve them forever if I feel like it!</p>
<p>Am I arguing with someone? This post has become very combative. Sorry!!</p>
<p>The point is, I did not feel like preserving them forever. I felt like wearing them! Let&#8217;s look at them!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Native</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911" alt="UD Native" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Native.jpg" width="480" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Native.jpg 480w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Native-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Native is a warm, baby pink. It&#8217;s a lighter pink than I would usually try, but I was into it! It&#8217;s opaque, but the very light color made it easier to see lines when I pressed my lips together. It&#8217;s a pretty sexy color that would work great with a 60s inspired look. AKA my very favorite kind.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Naked</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912" alt="UD Naked" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Naked.jpg" width="480" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Naked.jpg 480w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Naked-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Naked was my favorite of the nude colors. It&#8217;s a warm, rosy pink, and it&#8217;s a total My Lips But Better lipstick. It has great opaque coverage, and didn&#8217;t show lines like Native did. I did actually open this one prior to yesterday, and I always love it.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Protest</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913" alt="UD protest" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-protest.jpg" width="480" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-protest.jpg 480w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-protest-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Protest is another color I might not have picked on my own. But, Urban Decay knew better than I did. It&#8217;s a nude-brown color with a sort of peachiness to it. Honestly, at first I sort of shrugged at the color, but the more I looked at it, the more I liked it. It sort of reminds me of the lipsticks I was wearing in the 90s, but better.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Jilted</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914" alt="UD jilted" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-jilted.jpg" width="480" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-jilted.jpg 480w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-jilted-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Jilted is an old favorite of mine! I&#8217;ve been wearing this color for YEARS, and I love, love, love it in the new formula. It&#8217;s an iridescent blue based fuchsia, so of course I love it!! In fact, Jilted might be the color that turned me on to blue based fuchsias in the first place. It&#8217;s a really special color because the blue is really prominent, and it looks cool as hell.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Catfight</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915" alt="UD catfight" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-catfight.jpg" width="480" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-catfight.jpg 480w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-catfight-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Catfight is another fuchsia, but it&#8217;s more pink than blue, and it has a red undertone to it. Some people would probably call it red, other people would maybe call it dark hot pink. I think everyone would call it dead sexy. The new UD formula really performs well with their reds, and Catfight is no exception. It&#8217;s a super fun color that would look great on a lot of people!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>F Bomb</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916" alt="UD f bomb" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-f-bomb.jpg" width="480" height="640" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-f-bomb.jpg 480w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-f-bomb-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">F Bomb is described as a classic red, but I think it&#8217;s a little orangey. For me, this color was the standout of the bundle. I was in love the second I put it on! Again, their formula is a perfect match for these reds. The color payoff is fantastic, the finish is smooth and creamy and the coverage is amazing. I&#8217;ve been all about MAC&#8217;s reds for a long time, but F Bomb is going into the rotation. This is another red that would look good on a lot of people. It&#8217;s cool, but it&#8217;s almost warm and I think it&#8217;s very wearable. It&#8217;s even fantastic blotted down.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-917" alt="UD Black Friday bundle swatches" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Black-Friday-bundle-swatches.jpg" width="552" height="910" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Black-Friday-bundle-swatches.jpg 920w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/02/UD-Black-Friday-bundle-swatches-621x1024.jpg 621w" sizes="(max-width: 552px) 100vw, 552px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Urban Decay stepped up their game, did a lot of work on their lipsticks, and they&#8217;re a really beautiful, luxurious product now. The sugary fragrance is gone, and the obtrusive dagger handle is gone, but the bold colors we love are there. I adore these lipsticks, and I think they&#8217;re really worth the money. The new tube is sleek and easy to store, and the formula is moisturizing and long wearing, with the nudes averaging 3-4 hours, and the reds and pinks going as long as 6 hours.  I put every single one of these lipsticks into my &#8220;regular rotation&#8221; makeup bag because they are fabulous and basically perfect.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">What do you guys think? Is there a UD color you&#8217;re dying to try? I really want the super dark ones, but I haven&#8217;t picked them up yet.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Buy Urban Decay&#8217;s Revolution Lipstick at <a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/urban-decay/lipstick%2C-lip-stain-%26-gloss/revolution-lipstick/378.html">Urban Decay</a>, <a href="http://www.sephora.com/revolution-lipstick-P381305?skuId=1532076&amp;icid2=Urban_Decay_Must_Haves%20_P381305_link">Sephora</a> and <a href="http://www.ulta.com/ulta/browse/productDetail.jsp?productId=xlsImpprod5640306#">Ulta</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-revolution-lipstick-spectacular/">Urban Decay Revolution Lipstick Spectacular</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/urban-decay-revolution-lipstick-spectacular/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OCC Black Dahlia Look Breakdown</title>
		<link>/occ-black-dahlia-look-breakdown/</link>
					<comments>/occ-black-dahlia-look-breakdown/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 18:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Eyeliner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyeshadow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fave Looks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naked]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OCC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sephora Collection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=882</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Witch-ay Woman A commenter asked about the other makeup I&#8217;m wearing in this photo from my review of the OCC Lip Tar All-Star Mini set. I was like, duh, I should probably start including that information along with my photos. I guess I probably never thought about it because I am the worst and I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/occ-black-dahlia-look-breakdown/">OCC Black Dahlia Look Breakdown</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-734" alt="occ lip tar set black dahlia" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/occ-lip-tar-set-black-dahlia.jpg" width="672" height="896" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/occ-lip-tar-set-black-dahlia.jpg 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/occ-lip-tar-set-black-dahlia-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/occ-lip-tar-set-black-dahlia-768x1024.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 672px) 100vw, 672px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Witch-ay Woman</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">A commenter asked about the other makeup I&#8217;m wearing in this photo from <a title="OCC Lip Tar All-Star Mini x 4 Set: Anime &amp; Black Dahlia" href="/occ-lip-tar-star-mini-x-4-set-anime-black-dahlia/">my review of the OCC Lip Tar All-Star Mini set</a>. I was like, duh, I should probably start including that information along with my photos. I guess I probably never thought about it because I am the worst and I like to keep all my secrets to myself. Like, if you gush about my sunglasses and ask where I got them, I&#8217;ll tell you&#8211;but, inside, I really don&#8217;t want to. I know. That&#8217;s terrible. And it&#8217;s not even the grossest thing about me. Don&#8217;t worry, I get karma back on it. A couple months ago, I asked a lady at the farmers market where she got her sunglasses, and she was all, &#8220;I don&#8217;t remember.&#8221; And I was like, &#8220;Girl. Yeah, right.&#8221; It&#8217;s like Justin Timberlake says, &#8220;What goes around, goes around, goes around, comes all the way back around.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">So, the makeup in this picture!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Eyes &#8211; It looks like I used three shadows for this look. From the original Urban Decay Naked palette, I used &#8220;Virgin&#8221; for the brow bone and &#8220;Half Baked&#8221; for the inner eye corners. The bulk of the shadow, the wine color, is from a very old TIGI Cosmetics palette. I tried to find it, and unfortunately, it doesn&#8217;t look like they make it anymore. I swear this is not me just trying not to tell. I bough the palette when I was in beauty school a million years ago, and I probably shouldn&#8217;t even be using it anymore. The color was just called, &#8220;Wine,&#8221; and it&#8217;s not very hard to dupe; any wine color that leans more towards a plum will do the trick. I used a white pencil liner from the Sephora collection on my lower waterline, and UD&#8217;s black pencil liner on my bottom lash line and upper waterline. The mascara is Benefit&#8217;s They&#8217;re Real.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Eyebrows &#8211; Anastasia Beverly Hills Brow Powder Duo in &#8220;Brunette/Dark Brown&#8221; is my go to brow product. I use a light mixture of the two colors on a thin angled brush.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Blush &#8211; &#8220;Peaches&#8221; Sheertone Blush by MAC.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Lips &#8211; OCC Lip Tar in &#8220;Black Dahlia&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">There you have it! I guess I really don&#8217;t mind telling about makeup and beauty stuff. I mean, if I did, I probably wouldn&#8217;t have started a beauty blog. So, the good news is, my shadiness only extends to accessories! The bad news is, I will never ever start a sunglasses and bracelets blog.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/occ-black-dahlia-look-breakdown/">OCC Black Dahlia Look Breakdown</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/occ-black-dahlia-look-breakdown/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Urban Decay Spring 2014 Lipgloss</title>
		<link>/urban-decay-spring-2014-lipgloss/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 22:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Upcoming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=879</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The UD Spring 2014 line started hitting the internet this morning, and it&#8217;s pretty tame. I guess that&#8217;s ok. I just don&#8217;t get all crazy about sheer finishing powders. Don&#8217;t get me wrong! I love finding a beautiful new face product, but it&#8217;s less impactful in preview photos. Show me an orange lipstick or a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-spring-2014-lipgloss/">Urban Decay Spring 2014 Lipgloss</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The UD Spring 2014 line started hitting the internet this morning, and it&#8217;s pretty tame. I guess that&#8217;s ok. I just don&#8217;t get all crazy about sheer finishing powders. Don&#8217;t get me wrong! I love finding a beautiful new face product, but it&#8217;s less impactful in preview photos. Show me an orange lipstick or a hot pink blush, and then you&#8217;ve really got me excited!</p>
<p>I was hopeful when I saw there was lipgloss, but they&#8217;re all so sheer, and so similar, they all look alike on the lip. They&#8217;re pretty, but all the pictures I&#8217;ve seen this morning, had me like, &#8220;Oh. That&#8217;s nice.&#8221; I *am* interested in what the formula feels like, and it&#8217;s always good to have a nice nude gloss in your bag, so I might eventually grab one. But, I&#8217;m not in a big hurry. We&#8217;ll see. I didn&#8217;t think I was in a big hurry to get the Naked3 palette, but I still scooped it up the second it was available.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.temptalia.com/urban-decay-naked-ultra-nourishing-lipgloss-round">Check out Temptalia&#8217;s round up <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.musingsofamuse.com/2014/01/urban-decay-naked-ultra-nourishing-lipgloss-review-swatches.html">The Muse&#8217;s swatches are <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p>These aren&#8217;t actually available to buy until tomorrow. As much as I wish for it, I don&#8217;t get preview PR product. Probably because there are a million beauty blogs and I&#8217;ve only been doing this one since last May. And also probably because I only got out of bed long enough this morning to drink a Starbucks, and then I went back to bed until 12:30. NO KIDS, NO JOB, NOWHERE TO BE. ZZZZZZZZZ&#8230;.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-spring-2014-lipgloss/">Urban Decay Spring 2014 Lipgloss</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Naked3 NOW!!</title>
		<link>/get-naked3-now/</link>
					<comments>/get-naked3-now/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 14:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Naked 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=773</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WAKE UP!!! NAKED3 IS AVAILABLE NOW!! RIGHT THIS SECOND!! You can get it at urbandecay.com if you act fast. These palettes always sell out, so if you want it, grab it! Good luck!!</p>
<p>The post <a href="/get-naked3-now/">Get Naked3 NOW!!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774" alt="naked3" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3.jpg" width="400" height="400" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3.jpg 400w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3-300x300.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /></p>
<p>WAKE UP!!! NAKED3 IS AVAILABLE NOW!! RIGHT THIS SECOND!!</p>
<p>You can get it at <a href="http://www.urbandecay.com/urban-decay/eye-makeup/naked3/409.html">urbandecay.com</a> if you act fast. These palettes always sell out, so if you want it, grab it! Good luck!!</p>
<p>The post <a href="/get-naked3-now/">Get Naked3 NOW!!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/get-naked3-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Urban Decay Naked3 Palette Colors!</title>
		<link>/urban-decay-naked3-palette-colors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Naked 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Upcoming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Decay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=746</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Urban Decay released a sneak peek of the colors in the upcoming Naked3 palette today! The video is HERE on their Instagram.  It looks like the leaked photos floating around the internet are the real deal. The shadow names and colors in the video all match up with the names in these pics. Photo via [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-naked3-palette-colors/">Urban Decay Naked3 Palette Colors!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Urban Decay released a sneak peek of the colors in the upcoming Naked3 palette today!</p>
<p><a href="http://instagram.com/p/glcec6gEzW/">The video is HERE on their Instagram. </a></p>
<p>It looks like the leaked photos floating around the internet are the real deal. The shadow names and colors in the video all match up with the names in these pics.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://imgur.com/kAzQD0F"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-747" alt="naked3 leak photos" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3-leak-photos-389x1024.jpg" width="389" height="1024" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3-leak-photos-389x1024.jpg 389w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/naked3-leak-photos-1272x3347.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 389px) 100vw, 389px" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://imgur.com/kAzQD0F">Photo via Reddit</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">What do you guys think? Do you want it? I&#8217;m sort of on the fence. I&#8217;m not crazy about how rosy all the shades look in the pan, but I&#8217;ll have to see it in person to be sure. It&#8217;s going to be tough to pass it up. I&#8217;ve been able to mostly squelch my addiction to buying UD palettes, but these Naked products keep callin&#8217; my name!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/urban-decay-naked3-palette-colors/">Urban Decay Naked3 Palette Colors!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
