<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>boscia Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/boscia/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/boscia/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 19:56:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>boscia Pore Purifying Black Strips</title>
		<link>/boscia-pore-purifying-black-strips/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 19:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[boscia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skincare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=799</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The border on this photo is an artistic reinterpretation of what the inside of my pores look like. I think it&#8217;s pretty accurate. Also, it hides the fact that I am very obviously topless. Although technically, it&#8217;s true, please don&#8217;t tell everyone you saw a topless photo of me on the internet, I&#8217;d hate to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/boscia-pore-purifying-black-strips/">boscia Pore Purifying Black Strips</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-800" alt="pore strip" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/pore-strip.jpg" width="512" height="704" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/pore-strip.jpg 640w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/pore-strip-218x300.jpg 218w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">The border on this photo is an artistic reinterpretation of what the inside of my pores look like. I think it&#8217;s pretty accurate. Also, it hides the fact that I am very obviously topless. Although technically, it&#8217;s true, please don&#8217;t tell everyone you saw a topless photo of me on the internet, I&#8217;d hate to get the world&#8217;s hopes ups.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Remember pore strips? Remember how fun they were? Remember how they freaking hurt to take off? I do! Well, I forgot about that hurting to take off part. I remembered with a quickness though!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I&#8217;ve had this pore strip hanging around ever since a friend sent me a package of skincare products a couple months ago. I didn&#8217;t even realize it WAS a pore strip at first. I thought it was a sample of Boscia&#8217;s black mask, which I don&#8217;t care for at all. I&#8217;ve been putting off using the strip, for one reason or another, since then. But, lately my nose pores have been looking really dirty. Those are pores in the danger zone for me; sometimes I can squeeze them clean without causing a bunch of damage, but mostly I end up with fingernail marks on my nose, and a blemish that only I could see turning into a whopper that everyone can see. Pore strip to the rescue!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">When you do things like this, it&#8217;s best to do them after you&#8217;ve been in the steam and warmth of the shower, that way your pores are open and the crud is softened. So, after a long shower and a thorough cleansing, I applied the strip to my nose. 15 minutes later, it was dry and stiff. Time to pull it off!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">On the real, that part hurts. It feels like waxing your nose! But, you know, whatever. Pain is temporary. Clean nose pores are temporary, too, but worth it.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I peeled it off, and OH MAMA!! Huge success! The strip was covered in the contents of my pores. It even pulled out the bigger, darker ones that had really been bothering me. The overall effect was really great. My entire nose looked so much clearer. I hadn&#8217;t realized how clogged up it was!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After I removed the strip and stared at it all grossed out for a minute, I rewashed my nose with my cleanser. This is another important step; you don&#8217;t want to leave behind any remaining pore dirt all stirred up and half hanging out. They will turn into inflamed monsters the second they get the chance! Plus, you want to clean up any residue leftover from the strip.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After the strip and cleansing, my nose was a little red, but it went away quickly. I was left with a much cleaner and smoother looking nose, and my pores looked much smaller.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">These boscia strips are more expensive than the usual drugstore strips, but they&#8217;re nicer, more effective, and they include useful ingredients like witch hazel and charcoal powder. I&#8217;ll probably pick up a box for myself because the nose pores issue is a big one for me as I am genetically predisposed to having large pores. My dad has HUGE pores on his nose. It&#8217;s gross. No offense, dad.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Don&#8217;t worry, he&#8217;s not offended. He knows the insides of his nose pores are gross. When I was a kid, to our great delight, he used to do this thing where he would push up, hard, underneath the tip of his nose and squirt out the contents of the pores. It was like a super nasty Play-Doh machine, and we would squeal and run around all grossed out, but then we&#8217;d make him do it again. Super sick, totally fun! Dads!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/pore-purifying-black-strips-P288533?skuId=1406958">Buy boscia Pore Purifying Black Strips <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/boscia-pore-purifying-black-strips/">boscia Pore Purifying Black Strips</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
