<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dr. Jart+ Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/dr-jart/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/dr-jart/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 18:24:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask</title>
		<link>/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/</link>
					<comments>/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 18:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blemish Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dr. Jart+]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1089</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sephora, $7.50 for one sheet or $35 for a box of five A couple weeks ago, I hit the Sephora with a fellow childless enabler, and we had a lot of fun! Fun is a nice way of putting it. Rampage is a more accurate way of putting it. Like, did you know they have a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/">Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1091" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask.png" alt="dr jart mask" width="456" height="557" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask.png 456w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask-245x300.png 245w" sizes="(max-width: 456px) 100vw, 456px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/pore-minimalist-mask-P386840?skuId=1622380"><em>Sephora, $7.50 for one sheet or $35 for a box of five</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">A couple weeks ago, I hit the Sephora with a fellow childless enabler, and we had a lot of fun! Fun is a nice way of putting it. Rampage is a more accurate way of putting it. Like, did you know they have a sample limit at Sephora? Me neither! They way they told us, it seemed more like a suggestion, so we just kept hammering the samples anyways. I feel like my mid-level Sephora card entitles me to whatever I want in there. My VIB card, and my remaining bitterness over them making it seem like I had a job, and then not hiring me eight years ago. Last year, I made it a goal to let go of old grudges and annoyances, but that Sephora snub still stings. Especially when I saw homeboy that looks like Bobby fucking Hill working in there.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I like to just stay mad about not getting the job that one time so I don&#8217;t have to go back and try again. STAY MAD. That&#8217;s what I always say. That job is probably so hard; you have to deal with petty assholes like me all day. BUT, there is lipstick&#8230;.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">In my defense, it&#8217;s not like I just go in and demand all the samples and don&#8217;t buy anything. That&#8217;s not a rampage. A rampage involves damage inflicted on a personal level, too. If you&#8217;re not swiping your debit card in a near blackout state, sister, you ain&#8217;t rampaging.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Amidst the frenzy, in a fog of Tom Ford fragrances, I grabbed one of these single sheet Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Masks. Having never used a sheet mask before, I wasn&#8217;t sure what to expect. Since it was a sebum sucking and pore cleansing mask, I thought I&#8217;d get something sticky, or clay like. Instead, I got a fairly heavy mask that was absolutely drenched in a thin serum. Really, at that point, I was kind of confused, but, hey, I&#8217;m not a doctor! Dr. Jart is the doctor.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-1092" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/dr-jart-mask-photo-768x1024.jpg" alt="dr jart mask photo" width="546" height="728" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>-1 point for not having a mouth zipper.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After smoothing the mask onto my face, I realized, unless I kicked back, I was going to have a drippy mess to clean. I did not want that, and I didn&#8217;t want to waste any of that precious serum, so I put my head on my little pillow, and just <em>CHILLED.</em> The serum was really cool and relaxing, without any of the burning you can get from mint extracts.<i> </i>When the time was up, I peeled off the mask, and I was really surprised by how much serum my skin had absorbed. The mask wasn&#8217;t wet and heavy anymore, it was damp and papery. The directions said not to rinse, to just massage the remaining serum into the skin, and I am so about that. I hate washing off masks! I get so much water everywhere, it really might make more sense for me to just get in the shower. Same amount of toweling off, less water on the floor.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I wasn&#8217;t ready for how effective this mask was! My skin was smooth and clear, my underground sebum deposits were smaller, and my nose pores looked so clean. The work on the hard little sebum bumps was especially impressive; I&#8217;ve never seen a mask make  a noticeable difference on those before! Those disgusting little beads of oil are my #1 annoyance right now, so this turned me into repeat customer. Next time, I&#8217;m buying the whole box!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/pore-minimalist-mask-P386840?skuId=1622380">Buy Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p>The post <a href="/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/">Dr. Jart+ Pore Minimalist Mask</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dr-jart-pore-minimalist-mask/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
