<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>GlamGlow Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/glamglow/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/glamglow/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 20:51:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>My Skin System</title>
		<link>/skin-system/</link>
					<comments>/skin-system/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 20:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Aging]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Badger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beauty Tools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blemish Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clarisonic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fresh]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GlamGlow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mario Badescu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moisturizer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ole Henriksen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pixi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skincare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=884</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s post is going to be all about my current skin care regimen. So, I decided to get right to the point and show you a photo of my makeup free face. There it is. I&#8217;m not going to do that thing where I act like I&#8217;m super grossed out by my own bare face, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/skin-system/">My Skin System</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-885" alt="makeupfree" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/makeupfree.jpg" width="538" height="717" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/makeupfree.jpg 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/01/makeupfree-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/01/makeupfree-768x1024.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 538px) 100vw, 538px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Today&#8217;s post is going to be all about my current skin care regimen. So, I decided to get right to the point and show you a photo of my makeup free face. There it is. I&#8217;m not going to do that thing where I act like I&#8217;m super grossed out by my own bare face, because, I&#8217;m not. I think I look fine without any makeup on, I just think I look better when I&#8217;m wearing mascara.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Right now, I&#8217;m pretty happy with my skin. The texture is good, the overall tone is decent. I rarely get blemishes. It&#8217;s not perfect, as you can see, I have some dark spots. I also have a little bit of redness around my nose, but that could just be hormonal. I *did* have a giant pimple above my top lip, right in the center last week. It literally popped up out of nowhere. I did my makeup, then I got in the car to leave, and suddenly, there was this huge, pulsing zit. It really gave me a lot of trouble, but it&#8217;s gone now. Unfortunately, it left some scarring/discoloration behind. This is a new thing for me. Over the last year or so, my skin has changed a lot, and I think it&#8217;s an age thing. My mom has the same problem with scarring and hyperpigmentation when she gets a particularly troublesome blemish. Whatcha gonna do? I just gotta roll with it, and try to find the best products for my changing skin.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-886" alt="skin care products" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/skin-care-products.jpg" width="823" height="617" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/skin-care-products.jpg 3264w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/01/skin-care-products-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/01/skin-care-products-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/01/skin-care-products-1272x954.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 823px) 100vw, 823px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">These are the products I&#8217;m currently using. As you can see, I&#8217;m not into buying an entire skin care system from the same line. I think all of our skin is so different, it can sometimes be best to mix and match. You do have to be careful when you do this though, because some ingredients can interact weirdly, or cancel each other out. Do your due diligence and research that shit! I always read tons of reviews and information before I buy a new skin care product. It doesn&#8217;t always keep me from making a mistake, but I make them less often. When things go wrong, and they sometimes will, I just pull the new product and go back to what I was doing before. I let my skin settle down, and I try again. It&#8217;s an ongoing process, but I enjoy it. Also, I really know everyone&#8217;s return policies.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Let&#8217;s take a look at my ALL-STARS! LEFT TO RIGHT, Y&#8217;ALL!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00AU9EBTC/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B00AU9EBTC&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=B00AU9EBTC&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;">Fresh Soy Face Cleanser</a> &#8211; I did a <a title="Fresh Soy Face Cleanser" href="/fresh-soy-face-cleanser/">complete review</a> of this a few months ago, and I am still loving it. It&#8217;s such a nice, gentle cleanser. It doesn&#8217;t dry my skin out, and it keeps it clean. I&#8217;ve had this big bottle since June, and although I&#8217;m running low, I think I&#8217;ll make it through the end of this month. So, it&#8217;s not super cheap, but a little goes a long way. I pretty much only use this once a day, in the evenings. Either with, or without my Clarisonic. Hey, speaking of my Clarisonic&#8230;..</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.clarisonic.com/shop-our-products/clarisonic-cleansing-devices">MY CLARISONIC!</a> &#8211; Remember <a title="Worth it! Clarisonic Brush" href="/worth-clarisonic-brush/">when I waxed rhapsodic about my Clarisonic?</a> I love this freaking thing so freaking much. I love how it removes allllll my makeup, I love how it keeps my skin so soft, I love how it scrubs all my little face crevices. As far as beauty products go, it&#8217;s sort of a big ticket item. But, I&#8217;ve said it before, and I&#8217;ll keep saying it forever, they&#8217;re totally worth it. I use mine every 2-3 days, and pretty much every time I need to clean off a full face of makeup.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.pixibeauty.com/glow-tonic">Pixi Glow Tonic</a> &#8211; This baby is kind of new to the crew. I&#8217;ve been using it for about a month, and it&#8217;s been a great addition. It&#8217;s helped to clear up some rough patches, and my pores have stayed clearer. I use it every night, after I wash my face with my cleanser. I don&#8217;t wash my face with cleanser in the morning, I rinse with cool water, and then I follow that with this toner.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B000A0ADT8/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B000A0ADT8&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=B000A0ADT8&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;">Ole Henriksen Truth Serum Collagen Booster</a> &amp; <a href="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B007K6A1YC/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B007K6A1YC&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=B007K6A1YC&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;">Truth Creme</a> &#8211; I bought this set as my first shot fired in the war on my aging skin. I haven&#8217;t been using it long enough to see a difference in my dark spots, but I know I like the other things it&#8217;s doing. I use the serum first, then follow it with the creme. My skin feels soft and velvety, and it looks plump and bright. I use this system most nights, before bed.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.ulta.com/ulta/browse/productDetail.jsp?productId=xlsImpprod6200687">Mario Badescu Rose Hips Nourishing Oil</a> &#8211;  I&#8217;ve <a title="Mario Badescu Rose Hips Nourishing Oil" href="/mario-badescu-rose-hips-nourishing-oil/">written about this here before</a>. At first, I thought this product was kind of strange. But, the longer I use it, the more I love it. Although it&#8217;s an oil, it isn&#8217;t greasy. It&#8217;s got sort of a watery consistency, and it just sucks up moisture. It sucks it all up into your skin. I can&#8217;t get enough of how good this makes my skin feel! It has helped immensely with my dry patches, and my flakiness. I use this, in the morning, on its own; and I use it under my moisturizers and treatment oil.</p>
<p><a href="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0063NKM6K/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B0063NKM6K&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=B0063NKM6K&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;">Badger Damascus Rose Antioxidant Face Oil</a> &#8211; This is my treatment oil! I use this on the nights I don&#8217;t use my Ole Henriksen products, and whenever I feel like my skin needs some deep hydration. It feels nice, the price is right, and it lasts a long time!</p>
<p><a href="http://www.sephora.com/youthmud-tinglexfoliate-treatment-P375741?icid2=GlamGlow_Bestsellers_Carousel_P375741_link">Glam Glow Tingling and Exfoliating Mask</a> &#8211; <a title="GlamGlow Tingling &amp; Exfoliating Mud Mask Review" href="/glamglow-tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-review/">I&#8217;ve covered this mask here before, too.</a> After I ran through my initial sample, I bought the small jar during the Sephora Friends &amp; Family sale. I&#8217;ve used it once a week since then, and it has really helped to keep my skin looking clear. I credit this mask for helping to keep my nose pores under control. Those bad boys act up whenever they can. Jerks.</p>
<p>There it is! The system, the systo, the systrain! It&#8217;s all trial and error, guys. You just keep looking and trying and until you find the products that work for you. It takes time, but it&#8217;s worth it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/skin-system/">My Skin System</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/skin-system/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GlamGlow Tingling &#038; Exfoliating Mud Mask Review</title>
		<link>/glamglow-tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-review/</link>
					<comments>/glamglow-tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-review/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 15:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Face]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[GlamGlow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skincare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=541</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sephora, 0.5 oz., $19 &#38; 1.7 oz. $69 HOLLYWOOD, CALIFORNIA?! Am I supposed to be impressed by that? All across the top there? Because I used to live right in Hollywood, and I know for a fact it smells like pee there. Pee and booby glitter. That&#8217;s what Hollywood smells like. Now, there&#8217;s a real [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/glamglow-tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-review/">GlamGlow Tingling &#038; Exfoliating Mud Mask Review</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-543" alt="glamglow" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/glamglow1.jpg" width="448" height="411" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/glamglow1.jpg 448w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/glamglow1-300x275.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 448px) 100vw, 448px" /><a href="http://www.sephora.com/tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-P375741"><em>Sephora, 0.5 oz., $19 &amp; 1.7 oz. $69</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">HOLLYWOOD, CALIFORNIA?! Am I supposed to be impressed by that? All across the top there? Because I used to live right in Hollywood, and I know for a fact it smells like pee there. Pee and booby glitter. That&#8217;s what Hollywood smells like.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Now, there&#8217;s a real possibility they mean &#8220;HOLLYWOOD, CALIFORNIA.&#8221; That&#8217;s the one they show on TV with the sign, and the sun, and the palm trees, and the movie stars. That place exists, but it smells like pee too. There&#8217;s no way around it!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Anyways!!!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Since I brought GlamGlow home, I&#8217;ve been walking around singing &#8220;Just let your GlamGlow/just let it shine through/just let your GlaaaaaAAAAaaaamGlow, baby/feelin&#8217; oh so silky smooth&#8221;</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Coming to America - Soul Glo Commercial Full (Video)" width="696" height="392" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CGrasobHcKA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>It still works, right? As the jingle for a face mask? I think so.</p>
<p>There has been a ton of hype around these masks, and I was eager to find out if it was true. I&#8217;ve tried a lot of masks in my day, so I&#8217;m hard to impress. I go into most mask experiences not expecting too much. Although most of the GlamGlow reviews are positive, I did see a few that accused all the positive reviewers of being sheep who weren&#8217;t willing to admit that GlamGlow sucks. That seemed a little harsh to me. It&#8217;s cool if you don&#8217;t like the product, but don&#8217;t be a dick about it, right? I&#8217;m all for integrity in the beauty review game, but damn. Take it down a notch there, you big rebel.</p>
<p>I promise you I went into this more than ready to pan GlamGlow if I felt it was necessary.</p>
<p>Well, baaa baaa motherfuckers. I guess I&#8217;m just one more mindless sheep, because I really liked this mask a lot.</p>
<p>It looks and feels like most mud masks do, thick, cool and heavy. First, you stir it up to liquify it a little, then, you smooth it onto your face. I did struggle a little with the bits of  green tea leaves that were in the mask, because some of the bigger chunks were hard to stick down. I got it all plastered on though, so it wasn&#8217;t really a problem in the end. Other than that, it went on just like any other mud mask.</p>
<p>Then, the tingling started. It really walked the line between &#8220;tingling&#8221; and &#8220;burning.&#8221; But, right as I was like, &#8220;Ummm,&#8221; it calmed down, and didn&#8217;t bother me anymore.</p>
<p>After 10 minutes, the mask had dried very hard, and it was time to wash it off.</p>
<p>This particular GlamGlow mask has volcanic pumice in it, so when you rinse, it gets gritty, and you&#8217;re supposed to remove the mask in circular motions to exfoliate. I thought it was interesting that the &#8220;exfoliating&#8221; aspect was a good old mechanical exfoliant (washcloth, sugars, beads, etc.) as opposed to a chemical exfoliant, like an acid or an enzyme. I don&#8217;t know. It&#8217;s minimal work, but it seems like too much work for something that&#8217;s supposed to be a miracle product. Not that I think the pumice is bad, I don&#8217;t. It was just surprising because I think people want products to do all the work for them. And sometimes, you have to use your fingers, and exfoliate your cheeks your damn self. You&#8217;ll appreciate it more!</p>
<p>In the end, I was very happy with the results. I even said, &#8220;WOW!&#8221; to myself in the mirror. The French clay sucked out impurities and toxins, clearing up some dirty nose pores and deflating some questionable looking bumps, while the pumice sloughed away dullness and built up dead skin cells. I don&#8217;t know what the tea leaves did. Looked fancy? Got stuck in my drain? Yes and yes.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s the thing. Right now, I&#8217;m pretty happy with my skin. I&#8217;m able to wear minimal makeup, and everything is very clear and smooth. I didn&#8217;t think I&#8217;d see much of a difference, but I was very wrong. My skin looked a lot more even, and it really was, well, radiant. It was even better the next morning! The first thing I did when I woke up was touch my own cheek. The second thing I did when I woke up, was wake Jason up and make him touch my cheek. We both agreed that my skin was extremely soft. We were like, &#8220;What is that, velvet?!?&#8221; Then, we both agreed that I was extremely beautiful and that I would never get old, and that I would always have skin like this. After that, we agreed on Honey Bunches of Oats for breakfast.</p>
<p>Ultimately, I recommend this product. If you have very sensitive skin, be wary of the tingling, and exfoliating. Either one of those elements in an unknown product can really irritate your tender little baby face, and GlamGlow Tingling &amp; Exfoliating has both, one right after the other. Smear with caution.</p>
<p>If the price tag is a sticking point, go to Sephora and get a sample. Try it out a couple times, do the math, see if this mask at home vs. spa facials is worth it for you. They say you can use it twice a week, or as often as you like, but I would only go with once a week. Once a week is plenty for a mask this intensive. Especially if you keep on top of your skincare.</p>
<p>A lot of companies encourage overuse to get you to use more product than you need, so you run out faster and have to buy more. (HELLO, TOOTHPASTE COMPANIES! NOBODY NEEDS THAT MUCH TOOTHPASTE. And rinse and repeat with shampoo? Come on. That&#8217;s shameless.) I&#8217;m really, really not saying GlamGlow is doing this, I&#8217;m just saying start small.</p>
<p>Now, you can be all the things you always wanted to be&#8230;beautiful&#8230;sexy&#8230;</p>
<p>Sexual Chocolate, take us out!</p>
<p>http://youtu.be/mIdv52o0L-E</p>
<p><strong>P.S.</strong> I feel like all these <a title="Trader Joe’s Coconut Body Butter" href="/trader-joes-coconut-body-butter/">80&#8217;s Eddie Murphy movies/beauty review posts</a> are very telling about who I am, as a woman. And a lover.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/glamglow-tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-review/">GlamGlow Tingling &#038; Exfoliating Mud Mask Review</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/glamglow-tingling-exfoliating-mud-mask-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
