<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Education Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/education/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/education/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 18:27:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Santa Bunny: Beginner&#8217;s Bundle</title>
		<link>/santa-bunny-beginners-bundle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 18:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Beauty Tools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beginner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyeshadow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevyn Aucoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SALE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Smashbox]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Along with Fall (my birthday, Halloween, no more bathing suits), Christmas is one of my favorite times of the year. Christmas the day is whatever to me; I love giving and getting presents, but all that cooking and cleaning can get out of here. The month leading up to Christmas is awesome though! People are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/santa-bunny-beginners-bundle/">Santa Bunny: Beginner&#8217;s Bundle</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Along with Fall (my birthday, Halloween, no more bathing suits), Christmas is one of my favorite times of the year. Christmas the day is whatever to me; I love giving and getting presents, but all that cooking and cleaning can get out of here. The month leading up to Christmas is awesome though! People are nicer to each other, there are lights, and songs, and ornaments, and hot cocoa, and cookies! CHRISTMAS MOVIES! I&#8217;ve already watched &#8220;Christmas Vacation,&#8221; and &#8220;Love Actually.&#8221; I&#8217;ll hit &#8220;Scrooged&#8221; and &#8220;White Christmas&#8221; sometime soon. I&#8217;m emotionally gearing up for &#8220;Miracle on 34th Street,&#8221; and I&#8217;m saving &#8220;It&#8217;s a Wonderful Life&#8221; to watch with my mom. We like to cry together over that one. Stupid George Bailey gets me every time.</p>
<p>So, looking forward to Christmas, and inspired by a conversation I had with a friend, I&#8217;d like to help out with your shopping. Is my gift guide late to the party? Of course it is! Late to the party is my middle name. I actually like to BE late to parties. I wait just long enough for people to start wondering if I&#8217;m coming, and then BOOM there I am, drink in hand, making all your dreams come true.</p>
<p>This guide is for the budding makeup artist in your life, or for anyone who wants to improve their skills and get a little education.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>&#8220;Making Faces&#8221; by Kevyn Aucoin</strong></span></p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-832" alt="makingfacesbook" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/makingfacesbook.jpg" width="376" height="496" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/makingfacesbook.jpg 376w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/12/makingfacesbook-227x300.jpg 227w" sizes="(max-width: 376px) 100vw, 376px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0316286850/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=0316286850&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=0316286850&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;"><em>Amazon, $16.69</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a title="Making Faces by Kevyn Aucoin" href="/making-faces-by-kevyn-aucoin/">I wrote about my adoration for this book a couple months ago.</a> I&#8217;ve had my copy for nearly 15 years, and I still break it out all the time. I learned a lot about makeup application from my mom, but where her knowledge ended, this book picked it up. It&#8217;s extremely comprehensive and easy to understand, with clear instructions and pictures. Kevyn doesn&#8217;t just show you how to do eyeshadow, he shows you how to build your entire face from your bone structure up. His two makeup books are the only two I own. Nothing else comes close. &#8220;Making Faces&#8221; is an excellent guide for anyone, beginner or more experienced.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0316286850/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=0316286850&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=0316286850&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;">Buy &#8220;Making Faces&#8221; <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Sonia Kashuk Limited Edition Lavish Luxe 10 piece Brush Set</strong></span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833" alt="Brush set" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Brush-set.png" width="594" height="480" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Brush-set.png 594w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Brush-set-300x242.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 594px) 100vw, 594px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.target.com/p/sonia-kashuk-limited-edition-lavish-luxe-10-pc-brush-set/-/A-14637465#prodSlot=medium_1_16"><em>Target, $29.99</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">If you&#8217;re buying for a beginner, you probably want to get them brushes that are nice, but not too expensive. This Sonia Kashuk set fits the bill perfectly. Are they the most high quality, makeup artist level brushes in the world? No. But, they&#8217;re pretty nice. Every Sonia Kashuk brush I have has stood up to frequent use and cleanings without any problems. This set is a good place to start building a brush collection. It has everything a beginner should need, and some stuff they&#8217;ll probably have to figure out. That&#8217;s fun though! That&#8217;s learning! I bought a set of brushes in beauty school almost 10 years ago that had a weird shaped brush in it. I never could figure it out until just this year! Mystery solved! The new artist in your life will get a lot of use out of these brushes, and they&#8217;ll be glad to not have to use those weird sponge foam tipped applicator things. Do they even put those in makeup anymore? Am I showing my age? Wait. Does pantyhose still come in eggs? Does anybody wear pantyhose anymore?! The internet sure has changed everything!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">It doesn&#8217;t look like this brush set is available online, but they have it in store. At Target&#8217;s site, you can search the stores close to you for specific products, so that makes things easy.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.target.com/p/sonia-kashuk-limited-edition-lavish-luxe-10-pc-brush-set/-/A-14637465#prodSlot=medium_1_16">Find the Sonia Kashuk Lavish Luxe Brush Set <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Smashbox Wondervision Mega Palette</strong></span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836" alt="Screen Shot 2013-12-10 at 10.02.46 AM" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Screen-Shot-2013-12-10-at-10.02.46-AM.png" width="419" height="330" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Screen-Shot-2013-12-10-at-10.02.46-AM.png 419w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Screen-Shot-2013-12-10-at-10.02.46-AM-300x236.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 419px) 100vw, 419px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.ulta.com/ulta/browse/productDetail.jsp?productId=xlsImpprod5960730"><em>Ulta exclusive, $39.00</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a title="Smashbox Wonder Vision Mega Palette" href="/smashbox-wonder-vision-mega-palette/">I JUST reviewed this palette last week</a>, and it&#8217;s on sale now! How fortuitous! Last week, I talked about how I thought this palette would be fantastic for beginners, anyone who wants to expand their options without spending a lot of money, and anyone who struggles with palettes in general. I stand by all of that! With 30 shadows, 3 blushes and 1 bronzer, it&#8217;s got almost everything you&#8217;d need to start learning. The colors are wide ranging and beautifully coordinated with different finishes and consistencies. The palette even comes with clear, plastic instructional cards you place over the shadows to learn how to apply different eyeshadow looks. It was a great deal at $49, it&#8217;s a KILLER deal at $39. Plus, right now, with any $30 Smashbox purchase at Ulta, you get deluxe sample sizes of their fab Classic Primer and Photo Op Eye Brightening Mascara. Even better!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.ulta.com/ulta/browse/productDetail.jsp?productId=xlsImpprod5960730">Buy the Smashbox Wondervision Mega Palette exclusively at Ulta <strong>HERE</strong>.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Throw in a couple of lipsticks or lip glosses. NYX and E.L.F. both have cheap, but good lip products. And right now there are tonnnnns of lipstick and gloss sets that are crazy cheap. Add in some brush cleanser because it&#8217;s never too early to learn to keep your tools clean and well maintained! You can get everything I&#8217;ve shown here for $85. So you can get a couple lippies and a cleanser and still keep it under $100. This will all make for a good start, and a happy makeup lover!</p>
<p>The post <a href="/santa-bunny-beginners-bundle/">Santa Bunny: Beginner&#8217;s Bundle</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cleaning Your Brushes: Bacteria and YOU!</title>
		<link>/cleaning-brushes-bacteria/</link>
					<comments>/cleaning-brushes-bacteria/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Beauty Tools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cleansers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maintenance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Skincare]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=762</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When was the last time you washed your makeup brushes? A month ago? Last year? Never? NEVER?! DID YOU JUST SAY NEVER?! I just&#8230; I mean&#8230; I can&#8217;t even&#8230; That&#8217;s not ok. It&#8217;s not like I&#8217;ve never been guilty of letting my brushes get dirty. For a long time, it didn&#8217;t even occur to me [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/cleaning-brushes-bacteria/">Cleaning Your Brushes: Bacteria and YOU!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When was the last time you washed your makeup brushes? A month ago? Last year? Never?</p>
<p>NEVER?!</p>
<p>DID YOU JUST SAY NEVER?!</p>
<p>I just&#8230;</p>
<p>I mean&#8230;</p>
<p>I can&#8217;t even&#8230;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s not ok.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not like I&#8217;ve never been guilty of letting my brushes get dirty. For a long time, it didn&#8217;t even occur to me to wash them. I think I thought since I was the only one using them, it wasn&#8217;t necessary.</p>
<p>WRONG. JUST SUPER, SUPER WRONG.</p>
<p>Oils, dust, dirt, makeup, bacteria&#8230;these are the things that live on your dirty brushes. So then you use them, and you smear all that gross stuff around your skin. Doesn&#8217;t that sound awful? Keeping your brushes clean is good for the life of your tools, and it&#8217;s good for the life of your skin. Plus, it&#8217;s really easy and super satisfying.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-764" alt="photo-2" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-967x1024.jpg" width="557" height="590" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-967x1024.jpg 967w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-283x300.jpg 283w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-1272x1345.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2.jpg 1933w" sizes="(max-width: 557px) 100vw, 557px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">These are my dirty brushes. It&#8217;s been way too long since the last time I washed them. I&#8217;m really trying to get my skin in tip top shape, and I figured getting my brushes clean was a good idea. I&#8217;m not really acne prone, but I get those little white bumps. You can&#8217;t really see them unless you&#8217;re really looking, but I know they&#8217;re there, and I know what they are. Tiny little underground bacteria rocks. Gross. Have you ever tried to squeeze one of those out? That&#8217;s how I end up with a big hole in my face.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">First, you&#8217;re going to need a cleanser. You can use a mild shampoo, like a baby shampoo, but I prefer to use a cleanser specifically for brushes. Those usually have the added benefit of being antibacterial.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-765" alt="sephora brush shampoo" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/sephora-brush-shampoo.jpg" width="450" height="450" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/sephora-brush-shampoo.jpg 450w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/sephora-brush-shampoo-150x150.jpg 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/sephora-brush-shampoo-300x300.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.sephora.com/purifying-brush-shampoo-P208012?skuId=1069954"><em>Sephora, 2 oz., $7</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I use this brush shampoo from Sephora. It does a great job of pulling even the most pigmented colors out of my brushes, and a little bit goes a long way.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After you&#8217;ve decided on a shampoo, and you&#8217;ve washed all the dirty dishes in your sink, you&#8217;re ready to get started!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">First, thoroughly saturate your brush with lukewarm water.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-766" alt="photo 2" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-21-768x1024.jpg" width="557" height="742" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-21-768x1024.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-21-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-21-1272x1696.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 557px) 100vw, 557px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">DO NOT drop it down the garage disposal. This was a dangerous game I was playing here. If any of those suckers had slipped down into that disgusting pit, that brush would have been dead to me. Like, might as well flip the switch and chop it into a million pieces because I never want to see it again. So, yeah, get your bristles good and wet, being careful not to lose it forever.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Next, squirt a small amount of brush shampoo into the palm of your hand.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-767" alt="photo 3" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-3-768x1024.jpg" width="557" height="742" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-3-768x1024.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-3-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-3-1272x1696.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 557px) 100vw, 557px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Don&#8217;t skimp, but don&#8217;t go crazy either. You want enough to break everything up, but not so much that you can never rinse it out, or you waste a bunch.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Then, swirl that brush around in the palm of your hand. You can go crazy here.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-768" alt="clean brush gif" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/clean-brush-gif.gif" width="320" height="427" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Really scrub it good! You&#8217;ll start to see all the makeup coming out of the bristles, it&#8217;s pretty gnarly. Add more shampoo if you feel like it&#8217;s running short. Sometimes, I do this part twice. Especially on my foundation brush. That&#8217;s the one in all the pictures, as you can see, it was really dirty.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After you&#8217;re satisfied the shampoo has lifted out all the makeup and debris, give it a good, thorough rinse in the lukewarm water.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-769" alt="photo-2 copy" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-878x1024.jpg" width="557" height="649" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-878x1024.jpg 878w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-257x300.jpg 257w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-1272x1482.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy.jpg 1756w" sizes="(max-width: 557px) 100vw, 557px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I see that this photo is sort of redundant. But, I&#8217;m trying to be as detailed as possible! Rinse, rinse, rinse the brush. Rinse it so good. Rinse it until the water is clear, and the bristles feel clean. You DO NOT want any extra shampoo or makeup left behind. That would make this whole thing totally pointless.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After your brush has been fully rinsed, gently squeeze out any excess water, and then reshape your bristles and lay your brush flat, to dry.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-770" alt="photo-2 copy 2" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-2-768x1024.jpg" width="557" height="742" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-2-768x1024.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-2-225x300.jpg 225w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/photo-2-copy-2-1272x1696.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 557px) 100vw, 557px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I like to put mine on a towel so they don&#8217;t go anywhere, and water doesn&#8217;t collect underneath the handles. I also like to let the bristles hang over the edge. That way, they dry evenly and you don&#8217;t have to come in and flip them. I wash my brushes when I know they&#8217;ll have plenty of time to dry, preferably overnight.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">When everything is dry, just get the bristles fluffed back the way they need to be, and you&#8217;re all set! No more gross tools of cross contamination!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">How often you clean your brushes is up to you. If you use your brushes on anyone else, you have to wash them after every time you use them. If yours is the only face they touch, then once is a week is the gold standard. If you never ever clean your brushes, try to get into the habit at least once a month, and work up from there. It&#8217;s a good thing to do for your tools and your complexion. My brushes are an investment, and they&#8217;ve been pretty carefully curated. I&#8217;d like them to last as long as possible.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Keeping your brushes clean is the kind of thing that seems obvious, but I have a feeling that it&#8217;s the territory of people who are really serious about makeup. I know I sleep on cleaning my brushes more often than I should, and I&#8217;m a state licensed beauty professional. I should really know better! Let&#8217;s make it our Thanksgiving resolution to keep our brushes cleaner. Together, we can make the world a less bacteria laden place.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><strong>P.S.</strong> I cleaned my BeautyBlender with Ivory soap. It took forever to rinse it clean, and I haven&#8217;t used it since then, so I don&#8217;t know if it was a complete success. It LOOKS like it&#8217;s clean, but the jury is still out. I&#8217;ll let you guys know.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p>The post <a href="/cleaning-brushes-bacteria/">Cleaning Your Brushes: Bacteria and YOU!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/cleaning-brushes-bacteria/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Newbie to Junkie: Tips for Beauty Beginners</title>
		<link>/newbie-junkie-tips-beauty-beginners/</link>
					<comments>/newbie-junkie-tips-beauty-beginners/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steph Strickling]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 19:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Beginner]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lab Bunny Crew]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=751</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, I have a post from MY NEW INTERNET FRIEND, STEPH. I asked her to write a guest post after another friend, Denys, said she thought, based on Steph&#8217;s comments, she&#8217;d be a great fit for the site. After Denys pointed it out, it seemed so obvious! DUH. The only reason I missed it was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/newbie-junkie-tips-beauty-beginners/">Newbie to Junkie: Tips for Beauty Beginners</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Today, I have a post from MY NEW INTERNET FRIEND, STEPH. I asked her to write a guest post after another friend, Denys, said she thought, based on Steph&#8217;s comments, she&#8217;d be a great fit for the site. After Denys pointed it out, it seemed so obvious! DUH. The only reason I missed it was because I spend most of my time thinking about myself. </em></p>
<p><em>Because cosmetics and beauty have always been a part of my life, I often forget that not everyone has the experience and know-how that I do. It&#8217;s come up here before. Steph pitched her idea for a post about tips for beginners who are looking to step up their beauty game, and I was like, YES, DO THAT!! Her recently acquired knowledge is thorough and insightful. She&#8217;s a natural! </em></p>
<p><em>I&#8217;m super excited to have her stepping outside the comment box and into the spotlight! I hope you all enjoy reading what she has to say as much as I did. Thanks for your great comments and warm messages, Steph! I&#8217;m so happy your voice is a part of The Lab Bunny!</em></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-91" alt="*****" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/horizontal_rule.png" width="400" height="97" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/horizontal_rule.png 400w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/05/horizontal_rule-300x72.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter  wp-image-752" alt="Steph post photo" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Steph-post-photo-905x1024.jpg" width="487" height="551" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Steph-post-photo-905x1024.jpg 905w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Steph-post-photo-265x300.jpg 265w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Steph-post-photo-1272x1438.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Steph-post-photo.jpg 1291w" sizes="(max-width: 487px) 100vw, 487px" /></p>
<p><span style="line-height: 1.5;">Hi!  I’m Steph, fellow beauty junkie!  I’ve been a fairly regular commenter on The Lab Bunny and was extremely flattered to be asked by Sarah to guest post.  I’m a novice when it comes to makeup, especially compared to Sarah’s mad skills, but I’ve been actively working to get better over the last year.  I want to offer some advice on getting started to my fellow newbies, but first I want you guys to understand why I stayed away from makeup for so long.</span><span style="line-height: 1.5;"> </span></p>
<p>My first experience with makeup was a traumatic one.  I was in the fourth grade and had been picked to represent my school for a fundraiser.  Being the representative was a BIG DEAL; I wanted to look perfect for my moment onstage, so I asked my stepmom to give me a makeover.  She agreed, and I immediately started imagining what I’d look like once she was done.  I’d never worn makeup before, but even at that age I was a firm believer in its ability to make the ordinary into something more.</p>
<p>I remember sitting down in the dining room, surrounded by her beauty tools.  As she went to work, I envisioned what the end result would be.  I was guessing I’d pretty much look like Cindy Crawford or Jennifer Aniston.  As soon as she finished, I raced into the bathroom to check out how gorgeous I’d become, only to see this staring back at me:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-753" alt="mimi" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/mimi.jpg" width="281" height="374" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/mimi.jpg 281w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/11/mimi-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 281px) 100vw, 281px" /></p>
<p>I wish I was joking, but I had bright red lipstick, an insane amount of blush, clumpy mascara, and blue eyeshadow for days.  I’ve got nothing but love for Mimi, but I just don’t have the coloring to pull that kind of look off.  As I stared at my reflection in horror, I heard my dad call to me that it was time to head out.  There was no fixing this before school started.</p>
<p>I’m not going to get into the details of how that day went down for me, other than to say that the adults at my school were surprisingly polite about my brand new baby hooker look.  Predictably the other kids were assholes.  I decided that day that makeup was not to be trusted.  Some people looked good with it, but I was not one of those people.  I stayed pretty far away from makeup after this, except for lip gloss and mascara when I occasionally went to a school dance.  Luckily I was a big tomboy in high school, so it didn’t come up often.</p>
<p>It wasn’t until I hit my mid-twenties that my girly gene finally kicked in.  I started small by having mini spa days every few weeks, complete with manicures, face masks, and deep hair conditioning treatments.  To me, these things are basically the gateway drugs of the beauty world.  They take almost no knowledge or expertise to use successfully, so using them served as a good transition into girliness.  After a few months of that, I felt ready to start tackling makeup again.</p>
<p>Getting into makeup can be really intimidating.  There are a million different products, many of which you may not have realized existed before.  Below is the best advice I have for someone who’s just starting out.</p>
<p><strong>Know what look you’re going for, and don’t get overwhelmed.</strong>  There are so many different ways to do your makeup, and if you don’t get an idea in your head of what you like, it’s going to be hard to decide where to start.  Take some time to look at pictures and think about what speaks to your.  Do you want to look natural?  Dramatic?  Retro?</p>
<p>Personally, I’m obsessed with a perfect cat eye and really red lips.  When I started out, I knew that’s what I wanted to be able to do; it helped me get an idea of what products (other than the basics) I need to buy and what techniques I needed to learn.  Going to a makeup counter and asking them to give you an application in your favorite style is also a good idea before you start buying products.  A smoky purple eye could look amazing on you, or it could make you look like you’ve just gone up against Mike Tyson for a few rounds in the boxing ring.  It’s best to find that out before you buy the eyeshadow.</p>
<p><strong>Practice every chance you get.</strong>  DO NOT wait until an hour before you’re leaving the house to attend a party to become an expert on creating the perfect smokey eye.  You will fuck it up, you won’t have enough time/expertise to fix it, and the night will end in tears.  When the pressure’s on, stick with tried and true makeup you’ve done in the past.  Practice applying colors, products, and looks you’re never used or done before when there’s no rush.  One of my favorite times to test new tricks out is just before I wash my face at the end of the night.  Even if I completely screw it up, I only have to look at my face for a minute before it becomes a clean slate again.  There are still things I regularly make a mess of, but practice really does make perfect.</p>
<p><strong>Use the internet!</strong>  Seriously guys, it’s not just for porn anymore.  There are a million different resources available, including everything from product reviews to step-by-step tutorials.  Whenever I’m getting ready to buy something new, I do a ton of research before I take the plunge so I don’t get stuck with something I hate.  Once you’ve got a short list of products you’re interested in, head to a Sephora, Ulta, or department store makeup counter and test all the things.  There is no substitute for getting a product in your hands and checking it out for yourself.  I always feel better about making a big makeup purchase if I do both of these before I pull the trigger.</p>
<p>Some of my favorite online resources for buying products and getting tutorials (other than The Lab Bunny, of course) are listed below.</p>
<p><strong>Reddit’s Makeup Addiction Subreddit</strong> (<a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/MakeupAddiction/">http://www.reddit.com/r/MakeupAddiction/</a>)  Reddit can be an awful place sometimes, but their Makeup Addiction subreddit is fantastic.  You’ll find links to articles, tutorials, information about new products, and before and after pictures.  You can also post your own pictures up for constructive criticism and suggestions on your makeup.</p>
<p><strong>Reddit’s Makeup Exchange Subreddit</strong> (<a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/makeupexchange/">http://www.reddit.com/r/makeupexchange/</a>)  This is another really useful subreddit, and it’s one of the first places I go when I want to try a new product.  It’s premise is this: users post up lists of the products they have that they’d like to get rid of, or lists of products they’re trying to track down.  Other users can then offer to swap products from their own collection, or buy products outright.  Sometimes the products are used/sanitized, sometimes they’re brand new.  I’ve had great luck trading here; this month alone I picked up Urban Decay foundation and the Urban Decay Naked 2 palette for well below retail.  More details on how the swapping system works are listed on the site, and there are many other makeup swapping sites out there if this concept interests you.</p>
<p><strong>Temptalia</strong> (<a href="http://www.temptalia.com/">http://www.temptalia.com/</a>)  This is one of the greatest sites for product reveiws.  Not only do you get detailed descriptions, ratings, and gorgeous swatches to look at, duplicate shades from other brands are linked so you can check out all the options available to you.</p>
<p><strong>The Beauty Department</strong> (<a href="http://thebeautydepartment.com/">http://thebeautydepartment.com/</a>)  This site has so many comprehensive how-to guides for basically every aspect of makeup application.  If you don’t even know how to apply foundation yet, The Beauty Department can help.</p>
<p><strong>xoVain</strong> (<a href="http://www.xovain.com/">http://www.xovain.com/</a>) This site has a lot of good (and completely random) makeup tutorials.  They did “how to look like Bowie” earlier this year!  Alle’s posts in particular are wonderful.</p>
<p>I hope this was helpful!  I know I’m kind of long-winded, so thanks for putting up with my rambling.</p>
<p>The post <a href="/newbie-junkie-tips-beauty-beginners/">Newbie to Junkie: Tips for Beauty Beginners</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/newbie-junkie-tips-beauty-beginners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>6</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blends</title>
		<link>/the-blends/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 21:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyeshadow]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Links]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=567</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of my biggest beauty pet peeves is seeing unblended eyeshadow out in the wild. Like, I get it, these things take practice. But, DAMN GURL, YOU GOT A MIRROR OR WUT? How do people not see these things? It can just look really bad. That&#8217;s all I&#8217;m saying. Check out this tutorial: 3 Easy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/the-blends/">The Blends</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of my biggest beauty pet peeves is seeing unblended eyeshadow out in the wild. Like, I get it, these things take practice. But, DAMN GURL, YOU GOT A MIRROR OR WUT? How do people not see these things?</p>
<p>It can just look really bad. That&#8217;s all I&#8217;m saying.</p>
<p>Check out this tutorial: <a href="http://www.xovain.com/makeup/blending-eyeshadow">3 Easy Ways To Blend Your Eyeshadow Like A Pro</a></p>
<p>The first two blends are especially relevant to the looks most people want to do. That last one, the cut crease, that&#8217;s some more advanced shit; use only if you&#8217;re ok with people looking at you.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/the-blends/">The Blends</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Faces by Kevyn Aucoin</title>
		<link>/making-faces-by-kevyn-aucoin/</link>
					<comments>/making-faces-by-kevyn-aucoin/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 18:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Friday I'm in Love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How-To]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevyn Aucoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=519</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; I had no idea what I was going to run for today&#8217;s Friday I&#8217;m in Love. I have something for next week, but that would call for a photo, and my hair is in no condition to be captured online for all eternity. Have you guys noticed that my hair is always a mess? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/making-faces-by-kevyn-aucoin/">Making Faces by Kevyn Aucoin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-520" alt="fridayiminlove3" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/fridayiminlove31-1024x399.jpg" width="696" height="271" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/fridayiminlove31-1024x399.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/fridayiminlove31-300x116.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/fridayiminlove31-1272x495.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/fridayiminlove31.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>I had no idea what I was going to run for today&#8217;s Friday I&#8217;m in Love. I have something for next week, but that would call for a photo, and my hair is in no condition to be captured online for all eternity.</p>
<p>Have you guys noticed that my hair is always a mess? I feel like I talk about it nonstop. Seriously, if I didn&#8217;t think I would look exactly like my dad, I&#8217;d shave it off. Girls that can pull off shaved heads are dead sexy to me. Doesn&#8217;t it sound so freeing? My friend that does my hair would probably stab me to death with her scissors if I asked her to just shave it off. I like to make her do things to my hair she doesn&#8217;t want to do, but that would probably be too far. She&#8217;d snap!</p>
<p>Lucky for me, during a conversation with a friend last night, I mentioned this book, and my brain hamster started running on her wheel.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-522" alt="making faces" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-809x1024.jpg" width="696" height="880" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-809x1024.jpg 809w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-237x300.jpg 237w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-1272x1608.jpg 1272w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces.jpg 1619w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Making-Faces-Kevyn-Aucoin/dp/0316286850/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1375457882&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=making+faces"><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Making Faces</span> by Kevyn Aucoin, $16.01</em></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">You&#8217;re looking at my own well loved, bruised and battered (mmm&#8230;.battered) copy here. I&#8217;ve hauled this book around with me from house to apartment to pool house to house to apartment to house to apartment to house since 1999. You can&#8217;t tell from this picture, but the pages are coming loose and it&#8217;s full of random bookmarks. I love this book. I&#8217;m not exaggerating. I have actual love in my heart for this book. If they ever stopped printing it, I&#8217;d put my copy under lock and key, in an underground bunker, behind some of those lasers you can only get past if you do sexy butt wiggles all around them.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">It&#8217;s like this: if George Michael&#8217;s video for &#8220;Too Funky&#8221; is my origin story, then <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Making Faces</span> is my time spent on a Chinese mountain with Pai Mei, learning the Five Point Palm Exploding Heart Technique.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Kevyn Aucoin was an extremely gifted and talented artist. His techniques and advice still hold up, and even at nearly 15 years later, his looks aren&#8217;t dated. This book covers nearly everything you&#8217;d need to know about starting out in makeup, and taking your makeup to the next level. It has segments on skincare and prep, facial structure, shading and highlighting, brows, foundation, concealer, liner, lashes, lips and cheeks. It even has a little bit on cosmetic surgery. He doesn&#8217;t just tell you about eyeliner and lipsticks, he talks about different eye and lip shapes. He doesn&#8217;t just tell you about contouring, he shows you in an exaggerated, easy to follow way, where everything is supposed to go. He&#8217;ll teach you how to build a face that will highlight your best features, or, he&#8217;ll teach you how to completely cover your eyebrows so you can draw on new ones. This book is brilliant. Completely.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">After he teaches you the basics of makeup, he shows you wearable looks for many, many, many different faces and occasions, following that with more in depth costume and heavy transformation looks. The step by step instructions are easy to follow and well illustrated, and the photos are totally stunning.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-523" alt="making faces courtney love" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-courtney-love-1024x768.jpg" width="696" height="522" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-courtney-love-1024x768.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-courtney-love-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/08/making-faces-courtney-love-1272x954.jpg 1272w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>This is so beautiful, it hurts my heart.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I mean, look at freaking Courtney Love up there!! I&#8217;ll admit to having a soft spot for her looks through the years, disheveled and otherwise, but come on. This look, this photo, it&#8217;s really something ethereal.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><strong>SIDE NOTE:</strong> When I was, like, 13, I told my mom I wished I looked like Courtney Love and she was all, &#8220;LIKE A <em>HEROIN ADDICT</em>?!?!&#8221; And I was like, whoooah, yeesh, calm down. I just wanted to have real big boobs and be able to wear one of those clingy satiny dresses without rolls showing. Hey, one out of two ain&#8217;t bad.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">All the years I&#8217;ve had this book, I still break it out to check myself. I feel like I can still learn from it, even though, not s my own d, my own makeup skills are above average.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Please, please buy this book for yourself. I promise you will be completely enthralled, entertained and educated.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0316286850/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;creativeASIN=0316286850&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=thlabu-20">Buy &#8220;Making Faces&#8221; HERE.</a><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" style="border: none !important; margin: 0px !important;" alt="" src="http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=thlabu-20&amp;l=as2&amp;o=1&amp;a=0316286850" width="1" height="1" border="0" /></p>
<p>The post <a href="/making-faces-by-kevyn-aucoin/">Making Faces by Kevyn Aucoin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/making-faces-by-kevyn-aucoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
