<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jono Nelson, Author at The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/jono/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/author/jono/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 16:51:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>I Don&#8217;t Think I Can Spare the Moisture</title>
		<link>/i-dont-think-i-can-spare-the-moisture/</link>
					<comments>/i-dont-think-i-can-spare-the-moisture/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jono Nelson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Maintenance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Moisturizer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m super excited to be introducing you to my first guest writer! We used to be small town alterna-teens at a dark riverbed, and we turned out great. I don&#8217;t know about him, but I hardly ever go to dark riverbeds anymore&#8230;  He always compliments me on the way I do my corn&#8230;. I think he&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/i-dont-think-i-can-spare-the-moisture/">I Don&#8217;t Think I Can Spare the Moisture</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>I&#8217;m super excited to be introducing you to my first guest writer!</em></p>
<p><em>We used to be small town alterna-teens at a dark riverbed, and we turned out great. </em></p>
<p><em>I don&#8217;t know about him, but I hardly ever go to dark riverbeds anymore&#8230; </em></p>
<p><em>He always compliments me on the </em><em>way I do my corn&#8230;.</em></p>
<p><em>I think he&#8217;s awfully good&#8230;.</em></p>
<p><em>Jono Nelson, COME ON DOWN!!!!</em></p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-91" alt="*****" src="/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/horizontal_rule.png" width="400" height="97" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/horizontal_rule.png 400w, /wp-content/uploads/2013/05/horizontal_rule-300x72.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>I hesitate to reveal my deepest darkest secret because I know it’ll horrify the Editor-in-chief here at Lab Bunny, but I must be honest and admit my faults if I hope to grow as a writer and a person.</p>
<p>I don’t moisturize.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>It’s a commonly held belief that gay men hold the key to everything beautiful, glamorous and creative. Historically we have been innovators and taste-makers. Leonardo da Vinci, Oscar Wilde and Andy Warhol were all gay men that changed the course of human evolution in innumerable ways.</p>
<p>While I may have possessed this key at one point, I lost it probably around the time I started buying drugs from a Mexican gangbanger that I was never allowed to talk to. Basically, I’m bad at being gay.</p>
<p>Sure, in my youth I was running around southern California in skin-tight designer jeans and vintage band shirts worn to hell but then shit got real. In my mid-twenties, as a survival mechanism, I was forced to get sober. The good thing about early sobriety was that I was free of drugs and booze and no longer hurting the people I loved. The bad part was I realized how much I fucking hated my life, especially my day job.</p>
<p>After being clean for about a year I decided to finish up my BA in journalism. The more I focused on school and other things, the less energy I had to put forth in the aesthetics department.</p>
<p>Cut to today: I’ve relocated from Bakersfield to Los Angeles for school and academics have taken over my life. I pretty much wear the same four band shirts on a loop. My teenage, punk rock self would be happy to report that I couldn’t pinpoint the last time I washed my only pair of jeans that fit.This isn’t necessarily what I wanted, it’s just a byproduct of trying to make my dreams come true. I would love to be shopping for vintage leather but paying the bills and getting an internship are higher on the list at the moment.</p>
<p>My beauty regimen has also deteriorated to almost nothing. I put on sunscreen before I go to work but that’s about it. If I’m feeling fancy or have the time and energy to spare, I might put on a squirt of Lush’s Dirty body spray or slather on one of the zillion Black Phoenix Alchemy Lab oils I own (another addiction I should go to rehab for).</p>
<p>It’s not that I’m against moisturizing or even that I don’t own moisturizer (I have a pot of Lush’s Cosmetic Lad staring me in the face as I type this). My main problem is that I can never seem to make it a habit. I’ll apply it every morning for a few days and then forget about it or be too busy for it and then the cycle is broken. Cthulhu help us all if I don’t make coffee every morning but I can’t seem to find an extra thirty seconds to put something on my face to make it look better.</p>
<p>The other problem I have with moisturizing is that my skin is insanely temperamental. I’m not talking the occasional blemish during finals week. My skin routinely breaks out when the weather changes, when I try a new product or any time I leave my apartment. This situation is understandable in your teens and maybe even early twenties but I just turned 30 and shit has gotten embarrassing. I’m always anxious that if I use the wrong moisturizer, it’ll somehow make my condition worse.</p>
<p>I know that I’m not getting any younger. I’m also at a slight disadvantage seeing as how I spent a decade chain smoking. I need to start moisturizing and I need to start today, otherwise I’m going to end up with patchy skin and crow’s feet six inches deep.</p>
<p>God, grant me the serenity to accept the genetics I cannot change, the courage to change the skin I can, and the wisdom to moisturize on the daily.</p>
<p>Amen.</p>
<p>…</p>
<p>I’ll keep you posted on how it goes.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>(Ed. note: AMEN.)</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="/i-dont-think-i-can-spare-the-moisture/">I Don&#8217;t Think I Can Spare the Moisture</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/i-dont-think-i-can-spare-the-moisture/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
