<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized Archives - The Lab Bunny</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/uncategorized/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 17:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>On the Thumb</title>
		<link>/thumb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 23:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DIY]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floss Gloss]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nail Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nails]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=1087</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>That title is more like, On the Dumb. But, ACTUALLY, like On the Run. On the Run? They should have called that show, &#8220;Get Your Fucking Life for Three Hours.&#8221; I&#8217;ve watched that HBO special two and a half times, and I haven&#8217;t stopped yelling at Bey to kill &#8217;em all dead. She&#8217;s doing it, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/thumb/">On the Thumb</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>That title is more like, On the Dumb. But, ACTUALLY, like On the Run.</p>
<p>On the Run? They should have called that show, &#8220;Get Your Fucking Life for Three Hours.&#8221; I&#8217;ve watched that HBO special two and a half times, and I haven&#8217;t stopped yelling at Bey to kill &#8217;em all dead. She&#8217;s doing it, too!! I mean, I have this need for a beanie with one of those Roman soldier brush thingies on top, now!</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1326.jpg"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1326.jpg" alt="IMG_1326.JPG" width="498" height="744" /></a><br />
I&#8217;d stitch one up myself, but I&#8217;m a hundred percent sure the brush would just flop over like a melancholy rooster. And, also, I have no idea where you get one of those brushes.</p>
<p>On Saturday night, I had the champagne flowing, and the cheese plates stacked high. I don&#8217;t want to brag, but there were upwards of FIVE different kinds of cheeses. So, yeah. It was pretty fucking gross. I definitely got a stomach ache from all dat cheese. Worth it though!</p>
<p>In honor of the show, I broke out my <a href="http://emergingthoughts.com/Accessories/queen-beyonce-nail-decals.html">Sara M. Lyons &#8220;Queen Beyonce&#8221; nail decals</a>! I love these hilarious lil designs! They&#8217;re so perfect and cheeky! They&#8217;re also REALLY easy to apply; all you need are some small, sharp scissors, and a bowl of water. They&#8217;re basically temporary tattoos for your nails, they have the same application concept as that bitchin&#8217; ying-yang sign you bought out of the machine at the pizza parlor that one time.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1320.jpg" alt="IMG_1320.JPG" width="598" height="897" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Nails are one of my all time faves, Con Limon by Floss Gloss</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I fucked mine up by not using a lighter polish underneath them. As a result, Bey looks a little jaundiced. Jayndiced? Haha. Get it?<br />
Bey-Z looks better here:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/09/IMG_1314.jpg" alt="IMG_1314.JPG" width="616" height="616" /><br />
<em>See? On the Thumb. Whomp, whomp.</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Sara (probs too familiar) makes dope shit that really speaks to me. Like, her <a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/121781082/babewolf-sticker?">Babewolf</a>, or, her <a href="http://saramlyons.tumblr.com/post/29136201971/in-lux-we-trust-an-oldie-but-goodie">&#8220;In Lux We Trust&#8221; piece</a>, which is so awesome, it kind of makes me want to cry. I just realized I&#8217;m gushing, and I was gonna be all, &#8220;I&#8217;m a gusher,&#8221; but that&#8217;s not right. Let&#8217;s say, &#8220;I&#8217;m a fan.&#8221; That doesn&#8217;t sound as damp.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://emergingthoughts.com/queen-beyonce-nail-decals.html">These Bey decals are available only from Emerging Thought. Buy them HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="https://www.etsy.com/shop/saramlyons">Check out other sweet Sara M. Lyons stuff, HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p>The post <a href="/thumb/">On the Thumb</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glossy, glossy!</title>
		<link>/glossy-glossy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 15:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; When I say the word GLOSSY, it makes me think of the word FLOSSY. Which makes me think of that Fergie song that goes, &#8220;flossy, flossy!&#8221; And THAT reminds me that Fergie had a song out that misspelled &#8220;tasty&#8221; on purpose just to make it fit the syllables; AND WE ALL JUST LET HER [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/glossy-glossy/">Glossy, glossy!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/glossyboxy.png" alt="glossyboxy" width="713" height="414" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/glossyboxy.png 713w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/05/glossyboxy-300x174.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 713px) 100vw, 713px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>When I say the word GLOSSY, it makes me think of the word FLOSSY. Which makes me think of that Fergie song that goes, &#8220;flossy, flossy!&#8221; And THAT reminds me that Fergie had a song out that misspelled &#8220;tasty&#8221; on purpose just to make it fit the syllables; AND WE ALL JUST LET HER GET AWAY WITH IT!! I mean, I can&#8217;t spell banana without singing it in my head like Gwen Stefani. There has to be someone out there spelling tasty with an e before the y just because it&#8217;s in that Fergie song. Irresponsible, Stacy!!</p>
<p>I wish someone would make a song that spells out &#8220;restaurant,&#8221; because I still mangle that word so badly my spellcheck can&#8217;t even help. Spellcheck is all, &#8220;restraint?&#8221; I&#8217;m like, &#8220;No,&#8221; and then spellcheck is all, &#8220;Well, I don&#8217;t know what you&#8217;re doing then.&#8221; I always end up Googling it.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve been thinking about glossy and flossy because I just signed up for <a href="http://www.glossybox.com/">GLOSSYBOX</a>! I was getting really bored with my Birchbox, so I canceled it a couple months ago. Since then, I&#8217;ve been looking for a new subscription beauty box to take its place. I thought I had settled on another $10 a month box, but then I found GLOSSYBOX. At $21, GLOSSYBOX is twice as much, so that sucks, but the stuff inside looks really worth it! From what I can tell, they focus on luxury niche and foreign brands, which gives you the chance to try brands and products you might not otherwise find. This month&#8217;s box includes a $25 Bergdorf Goodman* gift card in addition to your products! I was all over that! But then I went online to the Bergdorf&#8217;s site to do a little pre-shopping, and found out they sell precious few things that cost $25. I don&#8217;t really care though because I&#8217;m just going to put the gift card towards a new bottle of <em>luxury fragrance.</em></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996" src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/ahs-balenciaga.jpg" alt="ahs balenciaga" width="557" height="297" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/ahs-balenciaga.jpg 557w, /wp-content/uploads/2014/05/ahs-balenciaga-300x159.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 557px) 100vw, 557px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>(The luxury fragrance will probs be Balenciaga.)</em></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">I&#8217;m really excited to try GLOSSYBOX!! It&#8217;s supposed to ship pretty soon, and we&#8217;ll pop it open together when it shows up!</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Want to try GLOSSYBOX with me? <a href="http://www.glossybox.com/">Get your own HERE.</a></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">
<p style="text-align: left;">*Speaking of Bergdorf Goodman, if you like documentaries about beautiful, sparkling, expensive things and people, check out &#8220;Scatter My Ashes At Bergdorf&#8217;s.&#8221; I really enjoyed this movie. There&#8217;s a story following the creation and construction of the Bergdorf&#8217;s Christmas windows that was especially fascinating to watch. See it if you can. It might still be on Netflix!</p>
<p>The post <a href="/glossy-glossy/">Glossy, glossy!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monday Mini</title>
		<link>/monday-mini/</link>
					<comments>/monday-mini/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Cosper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://labbunny.zbucaao2-liquidwebsites.com/?p=207</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>YAYYYYY!!! *KERMIT ARMS* My lovely and talented friend, Jennifer Williams, came by yesterday and set up an awesome little photo corner in my house! I can finally take pictures of my makeup that don&#8217;t turn out yellow, and I can stop relying on posts about stuff I don&#8217;t need to swatch. She helped me out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/monday-mini/">Monday Mini</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>YAYYYYY!!! *KERMIT ARMS*</p>
<p>My lovely and talented friend, <a href="http://www.jenwillphoto.com/">Jennifer Williams</a>, came by yesterday and set up an awesome little photo corner in my house! I can finally take pictures of my makeup that don&#8217;t turn out yellow, and I can stop relying on posts about stuff I don&#8217;t need to swatch. She helped me out at just the right time, man, I was starting to run out of ideas! Writing a beauty blog without photos of eyeshadow and stuff is not going to win me more <a title="Baby’s First Giveaway" href="/babys-first-giveaway/">BEST INTERNET</a> awards.</p>
<p>This week, I&#8217;m going to finally show you guys that OCC Lip Tar I&#8217;ve been teasing forever, and I got some rad nail wraps that I can&#8217;t wait to run. Oh, I also got these SUPER DOPE polishes that I love so much they make me feel dizzy. Like, I look at them, and get overwhelmed with how cool they are.</p>
<p>I have to keep reminding myself this is not solely a nail blog, but what can I say? I love nail stuff! Just last week, I bought a giant tub to finally consolidate all my polishes together. I almost filled up the whole thing, and the only place the tub fits is under my bed. I&#8217;m obsessed! I love to stare at my own hands and make unnecessary gestures so everyone can see my cool nails. It was really bad when I first got my engagement ring. I was flinging my hands all over the place, and voguing in the mirror nonstop.</p>
<p>Speaking of Vogue, here&#8217;s this fantastic video of 23 years of &#8220;Vogue.&#8221; It&#8217;s so great. When Madonna is good, she&#8217;s amazing. &#8220;Vogue&#8221; is my very favorite Madonna song, I will always love it forever.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Madonna: The Best of Vogue" width="696" height="392" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pEvaNDOGnD8?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">That&#8217;s all I have for today! But, I&#8217;ve given you the gift of Madonna, and you shouldn&#8217;t need anything else. Don&#8217;t be greedy!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/monday-mini/">Monday Mini</a> appeared first on <a href="/">The Lab Bunny</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/monday-mini/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
